Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[soft, tense music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[intense music]
[water splashes]
[water gurgling]
[soft, tense music]
[soft music]
[dark music]
So, how'd I do?
Better, right?
Actually, you're two seconds
slower than your top speed,
which, as I've told you before,
subpar.
That can't be.
I've been practicing
day and night.
-Let me try again.
-Sabrina.
I've hesitated saying this
for a long time, but...
you just don't have
what it takes
to compete in the Summer Games.
Coach, this is
my whole purpose in life.
I have to be the best.
I have to be.
Please, give me another chance.
I've given you more chances
than anyone I've coached.
I'm sorry, I really am.
I have what it takes.
And you know it.
You've always known it.
[Coach Sharky]
Sabrina, don't do that.
Come on.
Sabrina.
We've gone over this before.
I'm married.
And even if I wasn't married,
I'm too old for you.
No, you're not.
You're perfect for me.
I think you need to go.
Coach, please, I love you.
You know how much
I love you.
I have always loved you.
Coach, please, don't go.
Sabrina!
You need professional help.
[dark music]
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
[water gurgling]
[soft music]
Where are you going?
Sabrina?
-Where are you going?
-Work.
Good.
Doing what?
Teaching brats
to swim, okay?
You satisfied?
Yes.
And you should be too.
It's great you're finally
doing something--
Great?
It's an insult.
I trained my entire life
for the big leagues,
and now I'm just a...
Well, we both know why
you lost your shot
at the big leagues.
Don't we?
[dark music]
Mom, I'm not in the mood.
[sighs]
[hedge trimmer snipping]
[dark, dreamy music]
Mr. Scott?
Hi, I'm--
Sabrina Jameson.
Swim instructor, right?
I guess the inflatables
gave me away.
Yeah.
Let me wash up.
Come on in and meet my daughter,
Ashley.
Sabrina, call me Parker.
[dark music]
Parker...
[Parker]
What would you like to drink?
Oh, water's fine.
You'd think since I swim in it
I'd hate the stuff,
but no.
[Parker]
Great.
I'll be right back.
[dark music]
Be right there.
[soft music]
Hey, you must be Ashley.
[running footsteps]
[Parker]
Catch a glimpse
of the princess?
I did, she's really pretty.
Totally takes after her mom.
Anyways.
My wife, Ellen,
had this beautiful pool built.
Because she thought it would be
great for family time.
Absolutely.
Yeah, and then there was
an incident
and now Ashley's afraid
of the water.
[dark music]
What happened?
Um...
It's okay if you
don't want to tell me,
but it might help me
to figure out
how to reach her.
Have you tried to teach Ashley
to swim yourself?
Yeah. I can't even get her
near the water.
And, um... how 'bout your wife?
Did she try?
Yeah, about that.
My wife, Ellen, um...
She's away for a while.
Oh.
Where is she?
Uh, she's with family.
[Ellen]
The job just started
to wear me down.
Pretty soon, I was...
drinking to face trial dates.
And then the worst day of all.
[somber music]
I had told
my 10-year-old daughter
that I'd give her
a swimming lesson.
But I was drunk
and I passed out.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
Ashley decided
she could swim anyway.
I'm lucky my husband
was home that day.
I don't know
what would have happened
if he wasn't there.
A mother is supposed
to protect her baby.
My name is Ellen Scott.
And I'm an alcoholic.
[knocking on door]
Ashley, sweetheart?
[soft music]
[door opens]
One second.
Ash, I know you're in there
and I know you can hear me.
I asked this nice young lady,
Sabrina,
to maybe give you
some swim lessons.
What do you say?
[mouths]
Let me try.
Hey, Ashley.
I'm Sabrina.
You know, I was just like you
at your age.
You couldn't get me
near a pool.
But then... one day
this great swimming teacher
helped me get over my fears
and now--
And now... Sabrina is training
for the Summer Games.
The Summer Games?
The real Summer Games?
That's right.
And if you wanted,
maybe one day you could be
on the national team too.
But we're never gonna know
unless you get in the water.
'Kay.
All right then.
Go on and get into your swimsuit
and I'll meet you outside.
[soft, eerie music]
All right.
I'm gonna sit right over there
at that patio table.
And...
[dreamy music]
do my...
work, but I'll keep an eye
on you the whole time, okay?
All right.
Now.
First thing we're gonna do
is touch the water.
[sighs]
See?
The other teachers
tried that same trick
and it didn't work.
Well, let's try stepping
into the pool together.
I'll hold your hand
the whole time.
Here, let's try
something different.
May I?
Come here.
Good job.
There we go.
Okay.
This is gonna take
a whole lot of courage,
but I know you can do it, okay?
Watch me first
and then you try.
[soft music]
All right, you watching?
You ready?
[blows bubbles]
[Ashley laughs]
All right, come on.
It's not bad, I promise.
Come on.
All right, you ready?
One, two, three.
[laughing]
All right, now splash me,
come on.
No, a real one!
Splash me, come on.
[laughing]
Come on.
[laughing, splashing]
[humming dreamily]
[eerie music]
[distant humming]
You're doing it again.
What? What am I doing?
[soft, tense music]
You're obsessing
over some older man.
Who is he this time?
Oh, wait, I know.
The father of the "brat"
you had to teach.
So?
He's married, right?
That is none of your business.
[Khloe]
Oh, the hell it isn't.
I said that you could live here
as long as you promised
to never do this again.
But, Mom, this one
is perfect for me.
He's....
He's perfect.
Oh, Sabrina.
Your father left you.
And you going after
these older men
isn't going to bring him home.
[Sabrina]
Yeah, and you know why
Dad walked out?
Because of you.
You drove him out,
and I miss him every single day.
Miss him all you want.
He's never coming back.
And if you think you're gonna
find him in these other men,
-you're dead wrong.
-Parker is different.
His marriage is in trouble.
He needs me.
[Khloe laughs]
Okay, I'm gonna call
Dr. Gonzalez.
What? No.
He'll make me take
those pills again.
Yeah, you need to take
I don't need any damn pills.
Stop.
Give it.
Fine.
You don't want to get help?
Then you gotta call
this Parker
and tell him that you're gonna
turn down the job.
I can't do that.
I love him.
He's... he's the one.
[music intensifies]
What are you doing?
I said what are you doing?
I'm calling your client
and telling him you are unwell.
Mom.
Please don't ruin this
for me, please,
I am begging you.
This is for your own good,
Sabrina, and you know it.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Knock it off.
[grunts]
[panting]
[Parker]
This is Parker.
Hello? Hello?
This is Park--
[phone beeps off]
I said not to call him.
I told you don't call.
What is the matter
with you? Get up.
Mom?
[grim music]
[water burbling]
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter, splashing]
[soft, tense music]
All right.
Snack time.
Here we go.
One for you.
Is this what you drink
when you're in the pros?
Yep.
Dad, can Sabrina stay
for dinner?
Ashley, I'm sure
she has other plans,
not to mention other students.
[Sabrina]
I could rearrange my schedule.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
[Ashley]
Please, Dad?
You can make
your famous pasta.
Famous pasta, huh?
Sounds great.
[crickets chirring]
And, fortunately, I was
working from home that day
and just happened to check on
Ashley's progress.
I mean, had I shown up
a minute later...
Oh my God, no.
Yeah. So, that's why Ashley's
afraid of the water,
and that's when
Ellen and I decided
she needed to go to rehab.
Sorry, I didn't feel comfortable
telling you sooner,
-so I wasn't--
-No, no, it's okay.
Can I tell you something else?
Of course.
[sets drink down]
[soft music]
[sighs]
Ashley is the center of my life.
I haven't seen her
this happy in months.
It's all because of you.
Come on, I'm just givin' her
swim lessons.
No, I'm serious.
It's in the care and the concern
that you show for her.
I mean, you treat her
like she's your own.
I can't tell you
how much that means to me.
Whoa, uh, I'm still married.
Oh my God, I...
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
Look, I--I would be lying
if I was to tell you
that I'm not extremely attracted
to you.
But I'm still deeply committed
to my wife Ellen.
Of course you are.
I--I just got swept up
in the moment.
I guess I did too.
Ah, so, um...
See you tomorrow afternoon.
I'll be here.
-Goodnight.
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps]
Hey, babe.
Hi, honey.
Um, listen, I know
it's a little late, but...
[Parker]
No, no, no, no, it's okay.
[Ellen]
The doctor finally said
I'm ready to come home.
That's great.
[Ellen]
He says I can leave tomorrow.
I'll be there first thing
to pick you up.
[Ellen]
Thank you.
And how's my baby?
She's doing great.
I finally found her
a swim instructor.
Sabrina.
And she's training
for the Summer Games.
Ash loves her.
She's like a little dolphin,
I can hardly keep her
out of the pool.
[sighs]
What's the matter?
I wasn't there
for her first lesson.
Don't worry.
There'll be plenty more
to come.
See you in the morning?
Okay.
I'll be waiting.
I love you.
Love you too.
[aide]
I'll need your phone back,
please.
[clears throat]
[Ellen]
Thank you.
[soft, tense music]
[liquid glugging]
[acid hissing]
Fiji.
How 'bout you, babe?
[dark music]
[soft music]
[Ashley]
Sabrina!
Hey!
Big surprise.
-Come on, hurry!
-Okay.
Wow.
-Okay, I'll be right back.
-Okay.
So, what's all this
about a big surprise?
Ellen's home.
Oh.
Yeah, it's a little unexpected,
so I would appreciate it
if we could be discreet
about our moment
the other night.
Of course.
Hey, I'm just here
for Ashley, right?
No worries.
Oh, wait.
[laughing]
[Ashley]
You're gonna [indistinct].
Like, on day one
we had a splash fight.
So much fun.
You're gonna be so proud of me.
Sabrina!
Nice to meet you.
My name is Ellen.
So happy to meet you.
-I'm Sabrina.
-I know!
All I've been hearing since
I've been back is, "Sabrina!"
Thank you so much
for teaching Ashley how to swim.
My pleasure.
Well, I've got to go
to a business meeting,
so I'm gonna let you ladies
get acquainted.
Make me proud.
So, ready to show your mom
how great you are?
I will.
All right, let's go. Let's go.
[laughing, indistinct chatter]
Come on.
Did you see me, Mom?
[Ellen]
Didn't take my eyes off you
for a second!
You're doing great.
That's because Sabrina
is such a great teacher.
[laughs]
Am I ready for the pros yet?
You're gettin' there.
[Sabrina]
So, um, I usually bring
some snacks
for Ashley to enjoy
after the lesson.
Oh, how thoughtful of you.
There we go.
Granola bar and sports drink
for our world champion.
And for the adults.
One for you and one for Parker.
Oh, my gosh, no, of course not.
These are for you and Parker
to enjoy after dinner.
[Ellen]
Mm.
Thank you, but we can't have
these types of drinks
in the house.
Oh, why not?
I'm on the program.
Oh. Oh my gosh.
I'm--I'm so sorry,
I didn't know.
I'm sure you didn't.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow
for our next lesson, 'kay?
'Kay.
Actually, I'll--I'll call you
to schedule the next lesson.
Oh, you don't have to do that,
I'll just show up
at our regular time.
I'll call you to schedule
the next lesson.
But I've been teaching Ashley
for three times a week
for the past month.
She's been making
such great progress.
[Ellen]
And we appreciate that.
I'll call you.
Got it.
[tense music]
[engine revs]
You are going to love
going back to rehab, Ellen.
[Parker]
So what are your thoughts
on Sabrina?
Ashley's not having
a lesson tomorrow.
I canceled it.
It's obvious that Sabrina
is a little more interested
in you than giving Ashley
a swimming lesson.
[Parker]
I'm sorry?
You lost me.
I saw the two of you
talking to each other.
And?
What, you think
she's interested in me
because we were talking
to each other?
No.
Because she was
straightening your tie.
The hell
was she doing that for?
Come on, I told her
I had a business meeting.
She probably noticed
it was crooked.
[laughs]
Yeah, I'm sure
that's not all she noticed.
Babe, Sabrina and I
discuss Ashley's progress,
I pay her,
that's it.
Over a couple of cold beers?
What?
She brought over snacks
for Ashley
and two bottles
of craft beer
she claims were for you
and for me.
Now, why would she do that?
I don't know.
She brings over snacks
and drinks all the time.
She was probably being friendly.
I was a divorce lawyer,
remember?
I can spot women like her
from the next town over.
Is this how we're gonna
celebrate you coming home?
Just...
[sighs]
answer one question.
What?
Did you tell her
I was in rehab?
Why would you do that?
That is not something
that she needs to know.
[Parker]
I'm sorry. You're right.
It was a moment of weakness.
Okay.
But then... why would
she offer me a beer if...
if she knew I had a problem?
Look, I don't think
she was being malicious.
She probably forgot.
Babe, the main thing is she's
helped Ashley's confidence,
Ashley adores her,
and now she can swim.
Honey.
Get out into the world again.
Find a new job.
Volunteer. Do something.
But don't worry about Sabrina.
She's here to teach Ashley.
She's helped her a lot,
and that's all we need to know.
[birds chirping]
[dark music]
[sighs deeply]
[phone ringing]
Hi.
Steve?
Ellen Scott here.
Linda?
Hi!
Yeah, Ellen Scott.
Oh, you're--you're in a meeting?
Listen, I was calling
because I'm, um,
ready to get back to work.
You don't do family law anymore?
Oh, okay.
I'm sorry, I...
[sighs]
Listen, is Mr. Stafford in?
I wanted to let him know
that I'm currently looking--
No, I am not still in rehab.
[grunts softly]
[soft, dark music]
[sighs deeply]
[soft music]
[sighs]
[soft, tense music]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
Surprise!
We, uh...
we weren't expecting you.
Well, I don't mean
to interrupt,
but the last time
I came over,
I think I must have dropped
my sunglasses
somewhere in your backyard.
Can I have a quick look?
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
Wow.
Sounds like someone's
having a good time.
Yeah.
Look, I meant to call you.
Ellen decided that
Ashley's progressing so well
that she's ready
to go to the next level.
Great, I've arrived
just in time.
With someone else.
[soft, tense music]
What?
Yeah, um, we decided to get
a medal-winner to teach her.
Hold on...
I may not have a medal yet,
but I'm training
for the national team
every single day
of my life.
You can't just go switching
a teacher on a kid
like that suddenly,
it's not good for them.
I was also hoping
that we could sit down
and map out a plan for Ashley.
There's so much
I wanted to teach her.
Uh... thank you for helping her
as much as you did.
Can I at least
tell her goodbye?
[sighs]
[water splashing]
Hey.
Sabrina thinks she left
her sunglasses here
-the other day.
-Hey there.
Mind if I have quick look?
No. Go ahead.
How's she doing?
She's doing great.
Having a lot of fun.
I gotta jump, okay?
[soft, dark music]
Well, I can't find
those darn sunglasses.
Who knows where
I might've left 'em.
Anyway,
Parker mentioned
you found someone new
to teach Ashley.
I thought I'd say goodbye,
but...
I can't believe it.
Donna Dean.
The Donna Dean,
bronze medalist?
That's me.
And the gold medal's up next.
[laughs]
Great.
Donna's gonna help me
get to the Summer Games.
I saw you, little dolphin,
you're doing great!
[Ashley]
Mom, I have to use the bathroom.
Okay, but don't run,
and don't get water everywhere.
So, I hear
you got Ashley started.
Yeah, but, I mean,
how great for her
that you're teaching her now.
By the way, I'm a huge fan.
Well, thank you.
[dark music]
Wait, don't I know you?
You two know each other.
[Donna]
I remember now.
You were training
for the national team
with Coach Sharky
about a year ago.
I used to stand
on the sidelines sometimes
and watch everybody.
-Wait, who?
-Coach Wallace.
Sharky is his nickname.
Best swimming coach
in town.
But then you suddenly
had to leave the team.
What was that all about?
[intense music]
[water gurgling]
Are you angry with me?
What? No. Of course not.
My mom thought
it would be good
for a real medalist
to teach me.
That's why Donna's here.
Well, your mom is a smart woman.
You know,
if Ashley were my daughter,
I'd fire me and hire Donna.
You would?
Oh, hell yeah.
Oops.
[giggles]
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Keep up the great work, okay?
[soft music]
You have a fantastic teacher.
Okay.
Look.
It's obvious that
you bonded with Ashley.
And...
well, if you have the time, uh,
why don't you drop by
for Ashley's next lesson
and hang out with us.
I mean, if you want to.
I'd love to.
And just so you know...
Ashley was my best student.
Really?
Yeah, I mean,
look at her.
She's a natural.
Thank you.
And thank you for being
such a great sport about this.
Of course.
Ashley's in great hands
with Donna.
[Ellen]
Yeah, she is.
Go enjoy
your daughter's progress.
I'll show myself out.
Perfect.
[dark music]
Can't wait to redo this place.
[airplane engine roaring]
[Parker]
Well, Sabrina took that better
than I thought she would.
[Ellen]
And she said she'd love
to stop by and hang out
for Ashley's lessons.
Oh, really?
[laughs]
I'm sorry I jumped the gun
on Sabrina.
She really does seem
like a sweet young woman.
[Parker]
Told ya.
Mm.
See you tomorrow night?
[Parker]
Unless you've changed
the locks on the doors.
Mm.
I bought something sexy to wear.
In that case,
I'm definitely comin' home.
[chuckles]
[Ellen]
Oh, before you go.
Do you remember that photo
of the three of us
that was above the fireplace?
It's gone.
Babe, there's a lot of photos
above the fireplace.
Yeah, but this one was taken
after I got back from rehab.
The first time.
Wait, yeah,
I do remember the photo,
but... I don't know
where it is.
We'll find it
when I get back, okay?
I just don't understand
why it's not there.
It's always there.
Honey, you go to sleep.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-Love you.
-Love you too.
[energetic music]
[crickets chirring]
[tapping]
[tissue paper rustling]
[birds chirping]
[typing]
[doorbell rings]
[laughs]
Hey!
I'm here to hang out
with you
for Ashley's lesson
with Donna.
Uh, you're a day early.
Donna doesn't get here
till tomorrow
and Ashley's still not back yet
from school.
Agh, darn it.
Must have gotten my dates
mixed up again.
Anyway, I stopped by
this super cute bakery
and picked up some
gourmet cookies for everyone.
[Ellen]
Yeah, I know that place.
Wilka's, we go there
all the time.
Everything they make
is so great.
I know!
Well, since you're here,
come on in.
I'll make some coffee.
Great!
[soft, dark music]
[Ellen]
So you're all right switching
off lessons with Donna?
We'll try it
and see how it goes.
Oh, absolutely,
I think it's a great idea.
Honestly, thank you for even
keeping me on the team.
Oh, I hope peanut butter
chocolate chip's okay.
You won't get any argument
from me.
Oh, uh, Sabrina, um...
there's...
Thank you.
something that's been
bothering me.
The other day when you
brought over the, um...
-The beers?
-Yeah.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Parker told me
and I just wasn't thinking.
Can you forgive me?
Oh, of course.
It's just that,
as you know,
I can't have any substances
in the house.
No... alcohol.
Mm, no... prescription
painkillers.
No weed.
I completely understand.
Now...
You gotta share
the guilt with me.
Uh-uh, these are for you
and your family.
I bought some for myself
and it is gonna take
absolutely
all of my willpower
not to eat them
before I get home, so...
Well, in that case,
these are going
in the cupboard for later,
otherwise they'll be gone
before Parker and Ashley
even get here.
[laughs]
Polish them off,
they'll never know.
[Ellen laughs]
Joking, joking.
Oh.
[sinister music]
Ah.
Uh...
Gosh.
[laughs nervously]
Is everything all right?
Uh, I--I...
Can I get you anything?
[eerie sound effects]
I think I need to lie--lie down.
Can you see your--
see yourself out?
Sure.
Do you need me to help you?
[eerie sound effects]
No, I...
You're not looking so good.
[eerie music]
Sweet dreams.
[tense music]
Perfect timing.
Hey, little dolphin,
how was school?
[Ashley]
Oh, Sabrina, hi, it was great!
Uh, where's my mom
and why are you here?
She had a little headache
so she's taking a nap,
and I'm here
because I thought today
was your lesson with Donna.
My bad.
Anyway, I was about to leave
unless you want to show me
what Donna's been teaching you.
Yeah, wanna see?
[Sabrina]
All right, girly,
work that water,
let me see what you know.
Let's go, come on.
Yes, Ashley, look at that!
Oh my gosh, look at you!
You look so good.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, look at you!
Keep going, keep going,
don't stop now!
Yes, girl, yes!
Good job, I'm so proud of you.
How did I do?
Excellent.
I wanna do it again.
You should,
but I gotta go now.
I don't wanna get out
of the pool yet.
You don't have to.
But my dad says
no unsupervised swimming
or else he gets angry.
You know what?
If you want to swim,
go ahead.
I'm not gonna say anything.
It'll be our big girl secret,
'kay?
'Kay!
[Sabrina]
Just, uh, stay closer
to the shallow side for me.
Promise?
Promise.
[dark music]
[water splashing]
[water gurgling]
[sighs]
[water splashing]
[vehicle approaching]
[soft, sinister music]
[water splashing]
Honey!
Baby!
Babe?
[music intensifying]
[water splashing]
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Daddy, I was just--
[Parker]
What did I tell you?
No unsupervised swimming.
Yeah, and where's your mom?
Resting, she had a headache.
Then why are you
in here by yourself?
I don't need supervision.
I can swim, I--
[Parker]
Get out of the pool right now.
Ash, I'm not gonna say it again.
Baby.
[solemn music]
Baby, wake up.
[groaning]
Oh, where am I?
Tell me you haven't
been drinking.
No, of course not.
Did you know Ashley
was in the pool by herself?
Huh?
[she sighs]
You've been drinkin' again.
I can't believe it.
I cannot believe it.
[Ellen]
I... I wasn't drinking.
I trusted you,
and you did it again!
I... I wasn't, I swear.
Oh!
Where'd you hide it this time?
I know you put it somewhere.
[she groans]
Look what I found
underneath the sofa.
Now, why would it be there?
I don't... I don't know.
Yes, you do!
You put it there!
Ashley was in the pool, alone!
One of us is supposed
to be out there
watching her at all times,
you know that.
I... I swear, I...
I didn't even know she...
came home.
[she groans]
You blacked out.
No, baby, that's impossible.
I... I... I...
You're gonna have to go back.
[Ellen]
What? No! Please.
[Parker]
We're not gonna lose Ashley
because you can't control
your drinking problem.
[Ellen]
I can't go back.
[sobbing]
-This is Parker Scott.
-No, no, please! Please!
[unintelligible]
No, no!
Please, I can't go back!
[sobbing]
[birds chirping]
[grim music]
[he sighs]
I'll check in on you every day.
Ashley.
Honey, honey, honey, honey.
I know.
You gotta get in the car.
[somber music]
[engine starting]
We lost Mom again.
[sighs]
Yeah.
She just wasn't ready yet,
that's all.
Will she ever be ready?
[he sighs]
I don't know, Ash,
but right now,
it's best that
she be near people
who can take care
of her properly.
I can take of her!
I want to take care of her!
I know you do.
I do too.
But first, Mom has to learn
to take care of herself.
Are you still mad at me?
A little bit.
But it's only because
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I love you more than anything
in this world.
You understand?
-I'm sorry, Daddy.
-Come here.
-I'm sorry!
-It's okay.
[sniffling]
[vibrant music]
[splashing]
[water bubbling]
[clapping]
Look, everyone, it's Donna Dean,
world-famous bronze medalist.
How'd you get in here?
You didn't read the sign?
"Professionals only."
The exit's over there.
I'm not going anywhere until you
agree to stop teaching Ashley.
I'm Ashley's teacher, not you.
Besides, I'm better than you.
[laughing]
Okay... prove it.
You're on.
[tense music]
[splashing]
[intense music]
[water bubbling]
See? I am the best teacher
for Ashley.
[Donna laughs]
What is so funny?
[tense music]
What are you laughing at?
You think you got fired
because you weren't
a good enough teacher?
It's because you wouldn't stop
hitting on Mrs. Scott's husband.
-That's not true.
-Uh, yeah, it is.
Mrs. Scott told me herself
the first day I was there.
Yeah, well, did she also
tell you she's in rehab
'cause she's walking around
drunk half the time?
Oh, that's rich,
coming from a pathological liar?
You say you're training
for the Summer Games?
You haven't even been
on Coach Sharky's team
for over a year.
Yeah, word on the street is
you suddenly had to leave
'cause you kept hitting on him.
You don't know anything!
Maybe I don't know
exactly what happened
because I wasn't there,
but here's my guess:
You tried to hook up with him,
but he told you to get lost,
and you didn't like it.
That's it, isn't it?
Isn't it?
That's why they won't let you
on the national team!
You got a reputation!
Oh, Sabrina's a bad girl!
Look, I loved Coach, okay?
I loved him!
And he was gonna ruin my life!
I had to teach him a lesson,
I had to!
You had to do what?
Teach him a lesson?
You're sick.
I'm not letting you
anywhere near that kid
or that family.
I'm calling them right now.
[grunting, screaming]
[splashing]
[intense music]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[dark music]
Guess you'll never get
the gold now.
[ominous music]
[water splashing,
dishes clinking]
[laptop chiming]
[gentle music]
[sighs]
-Hey.
[Sabrina]
Been a couple weeks
since I saw you,
so I thought I'd check in.
[Parker]
Thanks.
How are you?
I heard the news about Donna.
It's unbelievable.
The police say she was taking
anabolic steroids,
say her heart just gave out.
How's Ashley taking it?
Not well.
She hasn't wanted to go
near the pool since.
Look, if you think
it would help,
I would be happy to come over
and give Ashley
some catch-up lessons.
I mean, if that's all right
with Ellen.
Actually, it doesn't matter
whether Ellen's okay with it
or not.
She's back in rehab.
What? She seemed perfectly fine
the last time I saw her.
-What happened?
-I wish I knew.
The thing is,
Ellen was always able
to hide her problem really well.
But this time...
I don't know,
she must've gone on a bender.
I've never seen her like that.
-I'm so sorry to hear this.
-Thanks.
Well, if you really have
the time,
I'm sure Ashley would love
to see you again.
I think some lessons from you
would cheer her up.
And vice versa.
-This afternoon okay?
-Sure.
Great. I'll see you later.
[clicks]
[sighs]
Perfect.
[ominous music]
That's right, yeah.
Down kick, then keep
your legs straight,
then do the up kick.
[bright music]
Yeah, keep kicking around...
Nice, nice.
[splashing]
[indistinct]
[phone ringing]
[splashing]
Hi. How are you today?
Feeling better?
[Ellen]
I... still don't feel
like myself.
Not even close.
[sniffling]
But I... I had to call
and see how Ashley was doing
after Donna...
I can't even bring myself
to say it.
Yeah, well...
Ash took it pretty hard,
so I decided
to bring back Sabrina.
I don't know what it is,
but those two have a bond.
Anyway, Ashley's smiling again.
I don't think it was a good idea
to rehire Sabrina.
I... I don't follow.
[Ellen]
That day
when she brought over the beers,
she knew I was on the program.
You told her.
She didn't forget.
She--she brought those beers
on purpose.
You remember that
but you don't remember
passing out
in the middle of the day
with our daughter
in the pool by herself.
I don't know what happened,
but I swear,
I was not drinking that day,
I wasn't.
Instead of fixating on Sabrina
bringing over those beers,
why don't you come clean
about the fact
that you were drinking that day?
I wasn't drinking!
[intense music]
And I don't know what happened,
but I think Sabrina
did something.
Just like she did
with those beers,
she... she did something.
You're not making any sense.
[Ellen]
I can't remember.
-Yeah, because you blacked out.
-No.
Trust me, I swear, I...
[Parker]
I can't!
Sabrina is trouble.
She's the one who's lying.
Yeah, well, she's not the one
that left our daughter
in the pool unattended.
Baby, I--I swear. Please.
[Parker]
I've gotta go.
[sobs]
[Parker]
You're teaming up
on me now, okay.
[laughter]
Can you come back tomorrow?
Oh, tomorrow, I don't know.
Let me... let me check.
[gentle music]
It's looking like...
I can make it.
Yes!
Can Sabrina stay for dinner
tomorrow night too?
Ash, we can't take
all of her time.
Why not?
[Parker]
We'll see.
For now, brush your teeth
and get to bed.
Only if Sabrina tucks me in.
Be right back.
[laughing]
Did your mom ever tuck you in
when you were a kid?
No. My mother
never really had time for me.
[tender music]
She didn't really love me.
What is it, sweetie?
I don't think my mom
loves me either.
[Sabrina]
Of course she does.
No, she doesn't.
She's never here,
she keeps making mistakes.
Ashley, we all make mistakes.
Your mom loves you,
and your dad does too.
Do you know how lucky you are
to have such a fantastic dad?
Last time I saw my dad,
I was five years old.
He used to take me swimming.
He and my mom
were always arguing.
He was trying his best,
but... it was never good enough
for her.
He couldn't take it.
One day, packed his suitcase,
kissed me goodbye,
and I never saw him again.
I think about Daddy every day.
I wish I could bring him back,
but... I can't.
Anyway, trust me.
Your mom and dad love you.
And so do I.
Good night, little dolphin.
Good night, big dolphin.
[laughing]
Let's see, all right.
We have candles...
That's for the diffuser.
Where's the diffuser?
There it is, okay, um...
Wait, you brought
all this here for me?
[mellow music]
Stress relief.
This stuff helps,
and trust me, you need it.
There is... one more thing
you should do.
[water splashing]
Doesn't this feel great?
It does.
You know, you should give
yourself daily swim breaks.
I mean, you clearly work out.
[chuckles]
Mainly weights and jogging.
Okay, so,
make swim dates
with your daughter then.
I bet she'd love that.
That was actually
my original plan.
Thank you for reminding me.
Race you to the other side?
[splashing]
[intense music]
[laughing]
Okay.
You win.
I'm no match for you.
I bet you could be.
Sabrina...
That's my name.
I forgot to mention...
this is the other way
to relieve stress.
[laughing]
[soft music]
You have to get up early?
No, I can sleep in.
-Good.
-Yeah, but this coming Tuesday,
I have to go to New York
for two weeks.
Yeah, lately I pay the neighbor
to look over Ashley
while I'm gone, but...
I'll do it.
You would?
You could stay here.
I would love that.
I've been reading a lot
about substance abuse.
Addiction.
Ellen, you, and Ashley
will be dealing with this
for the rest of Ellen's life.
[sighs]
You're always telling me
you have to think
about Ashley's future,
but... she deserves a mother
who's reliable,
who's gonna be there for her.
Doesn't she?
She does.
I could be that for her.
[Ellen]
I don't even remember
how I got here this time.
But I do know...
I never want to be here again.
I love you all,
but... I miss my family,
and I want to go home.
[solemn music]
My name is Ellen Scott,
and I'm an alcoholic.
[applause]
Good job.
[sighs]
Vicky, why don't you go next?
Mm, sure, um...
I started drinking
when I was 12.
My friend invited me over
and her parents weren't home,
so we thought
that it would be cool
to drink some
of her dad's beers,
and then we drank some more.
It was fun,
and we just kept drinkin' 'em.
We turned on the TV,
and they were showing
that old movie, Jaws.
[dark music]
Okay, maybe some of you
don't remember it,
but it was about
this huge killer shark.
[voice echoing]
Huge killer shark.
[Donna]
You were training
for the national team
with Coach Sharky
about a year ago.
-Wait, who?
-Coach Wallace.
Sharky is his nickname.
[Vicky]
And it really gets me
because my niece is 12 now
and when I--
[Ellen]
Excuse me.
Hey, Ellen.
Hey, we're not done yet here.
Jerry, could I use my phone
for a minute?
Good afternoon to you too.
You know the rules:
Phone calls only
during scheduled times
with supervision.
It's my friend's birthday
and... last year I forgot it.
I just want to send her a text
and let her know
how much she means to me.
I just need a minute... or two.
I'll be standing
right here in front of you.
Two minutes. Go.
[phone ringing]
[Jerry]
Reception.
He's doing what?
Well, where's the--
Okay, you know what, never mind.
Coming up.
Lucky you, I got a situation
on the third floor.
You just bought yourself
two more minutes.
Thank you.
[phone dialing]
-Hello?
-Hi!
Coach Sharky Wallace?
[Coach Sharky]
Yeah, who's this?
Hi, my--my name is Ellen Scott.
I'm--I'm calling about a swimmer
that you coached last year,
a young woman by the name
of Sabrina Jameson.
[Coach Sharky]
I can't discuss
my students with strangers.
-Goodbye.
-Hello?
Coach Sharky?
Hello?
[sighs]
[car beeping]
[dramatic music]
[birds chirping]
[Parker]
You looking forward
to seeing Charlotte today?
That's why I love Saturdays
so much!
And her mom always makes us
popcorn when we watch movies.
[gentle music]
Hey, how would you feel
about Sabrina spending
a little more time with us?
You mean, like, moving in?
Not exactly.
You know I have to go
to New York in a couple of days,
so instead of dropping you off
at Mrs. Miller's,
I thought maybe Sabrina
could come stay here with you.
That'd be great,
I love Sabrina!
Uh, then I guess...
Mom's not coming back?
[sighs]
Of course she is.
But I just don't know when.
Meanwhile, it might be nice
to have Sabrina around here
a little more,
if that's okay with you.
It's okay.
[Parker]
Good, but Sabrina
will never take the place
of your mom.
I just want to be clear
about that.
Dad, I know that.
You have fun. If you need
anything, let me know, call me.
Okay, I know.
-I love you.
-I do too!
Let me get the door.
-Thank you, Dad.
-Thank you so much again.
All right, you ladies have fun.
[door closes]
[bright, eerie music]
[Sabrina]
Daddy...
[intense, ominous music]
[tense music]
[Sabrina]
I stopped by
this super cute bakery
and picked up gourmet cookies
for everyone.
[Ellen]
Coach Sharky?
-Yeah, who are you?
-Oh, I...
I am sorry to bother you, but...
You're the one who called
earlier, aren't you?
Yes, but please let me explain.
A few months ago,
my husband hired Sabrina
to give our daughter
swimming lessons.
Sabrina said that she was
training for the Summer Games,
but later, I found out
that she wasn't
and she hadn't been
for a year.
I am convinced that Sabrina
has been lying to us.
My husband doesn't think so,
but I do.
Please, can you help me?
[Coach Sharky]
I feel partially responsible.
I just... I didn't think
that she'd continue with the...
Continue to what?
Sabrina was one of my students.
She showed some promise
in the beginning,
but then she started
to have some issues.
[intense music]
[Sabrina]
You're perfect for me.
You know how much I love you!
I've always loved you!
[splashing]
You're the first person I told.
I didn't call the police
because,
even though she tried
to kill me,
I felt guilty
about kickin' her off the team.
I mean, I didn't want
to completely destroy her life.
You were a lot more generous
than I would've been.
Later, I found out that I wasn't
her first, um... obsession.
She has a thing for older men,
and if they reject her,
she freaks out
and tries to kill 'em.
[dramatic music]
I think one of those older men
happens to be my husband.
[phone ringing]
Everything okay?
Listen to me carefully
and do not hang up.
What's goin' on?
You sound like you're in a car.
Where are you?
[Ellen]
That's not important.
I just talked
to Sabrina's old coach.
What? Why?
Why would you do that?
[Ellen]
I remembered something
Donna said.
It came rushing back
to me today.
Sabrina stopped training
for the Summer Games
and had to suddenly leave
her team a year ago.
I had to find out why.
Sabrina told me she's been
training every single day.
[Ellen]
Yeah, well, she hasn't been.
Okay, well, maybe she said that
just to get the job.
One way or another,
Ashley can swim now.
[Ellen]
Listen to me.
Her coach said he had to kick
Sabrina off the team
because she kept hitting on him.
When he rejected her,
she tried to kill him!
Hello, did you hear what I said?
She tried to kill him!
I... I can't believe that.
Yeah, well, you better.
He wasn't the first one.
It's a pattern she has
with older men who reject her.
Be straight with me,
have you been drinking?
[Ellen]
I am stone-cold sober!
That's the other thing.
I remember that day now clearly.
I didn't drink anything!
Sabrina came over with
a box of cookies from Wilka's.
I had some, she didn't,
because she laced them
with drugs.
That doesn't make any sense.
[Ellen]
Yes, it does!
It all makes sense!
She drugged me
to get me out of the picture
because she wants
to get rid of me!
Okay, well, how do you explain
the bottle of whiskey I found?
[Ellen]
Sabrina put it there!
It had to be her!
Okay, I admit, I used to hide
bottles all over the house,
but, under the sofa?
Come on! That's for amateurs!
[doorbell ringing]
Hold on, someone's at the door.
[door opening]
Morning!
-Business call.
-Okay.
Listen, I...
[Ellen]
She's already there, isn't she?
Parker, she is dangerous!
She cannot be
around you or Ashley!
[Parker]
I have to go.
[birds chirping]
[grim music]
It's a beautiful pool, isn't it?
Yeah, it's perfect.
Ash and I are gonna have
so much fun swimming in it,
and even more fun
when you come back and join us.
Yeah, you know,
I'm not leaving
until Tuesday though.
It's only Saturday.
Oh, I know.
I just wanted to get
a head start, you know?
Learn my way around the house,
make sure I know
where everything is.
For Ashley.
By the way,
how's your training going?
You know, for the Summer Games?
-Great.
-I guess I should know this
by now,
but how often do you train?
-As often as I can.
-The reason why I'm asking is
I was hoping I could consult
with your coach
to see if I can get Ashley
into the accelerated program.
She's been doing so well.
I can look into that for you.
That might be difficult, though,
since you're not training
for the Summer Games.
I don't like when people
lie to me, Sabrina.
I'm not lying.
Good, glad to hear that.
I feel so much better.
Although, Ellen told me
that you brought over
a box of cookies.
She ate them and you didn't.
Why not?
I wasn't hungry.
I'm thinking you didn't eat them
because you put drugs in them,
and whatever you put in them
knocked Ellen out.
That's crazy!
Why would I do that?
So I would think Ellen
was drinking again, that's why.
And that bottle of whiskey
under the sofa,
I'm guessing
you didn't do that either?
Everything's going so well.
Why are you playing
this game with me?
Why have you been lying to me
from the moment
that you walked into my house?
You were never training
for the Summer Games.
You got kicked off the team
because you tried to kill
your coach!
That's not true!
Ellen tracked him down,
he told her everything,
so don't lie to me anymore,
Sabrina!
I wasn't trying to kill him!
He was trying to kill me!
I loved him, and he was trying
to walk away from me!
But that--that doesn't matter
anymore,
because I have you and Ashley.
Look...
We're a family now.
Sabrina, I don't know
what you're talking about,
but you need to go right now.
Go where?
I gave up everything
to be with you.
We're--we're gonna start
a new life together,
you, me, and Ashley.
I'm gonna say this
one more time:
You need to go.
But... but we're together now.
You--you love me.
Like hell I do!
Get out!
I'm calling the police.
[music intensifying]
[grunting]
[Sabrina]
You don't deserve me!
[water bubbling]
[grunting]
[Ellen]
Hey!
[whacks]
[splashing]
Parker!
[gentle music]
[gasping]
Come here.
[breathing heavily]
Are you okay?
[coughing]
[splashing]
-I'll call 9-1-1.
-Okay.
[grunting]
We're at 4202
South Parallel Avenue.
Come on, Sabrina.
[gagging]
[coughing]
[breathing heavily]
[mellow music]
[police radio chatter]
[handcuffs clicking]
[birds chirping]
[bright music]
[splashing]
[shouting]
[tense music]