Downloaded from
Fm Movie
By Ferymaleha
What's wrong with you?
These people have paid to come and watch.
-Where do you think you are going?
-Hey, man, we're waiting for you.
-Come on, sing a song.
-No please, I'll handle it.
This girl paid to come and listen to
a song by Louw… Louw… Louw van Lier.
Keep quiet, please.
I don't give a damn who he thinks he is.
Just give us a song.
No.
I'll send you to your grave!
Who do you think you are?
Everybody told me
Louw van Lier is a nobody.
But for Karien's sake,
I decided to give you another chance.
Now I see they're right. You are a nobody.
And don't think you can
ever come back here!
Nobody… will give you a chance again!
Because nobody
will ever remember you!
Matewis!
The boxes.
Sorry, did you… leave it, I will.
Perfect timing, as always!
I'm done.
Why didn't you mention
anything about Louw coming?
I only found out this morning.
This morning?
I told him our home will always be open.
He's my brother, Matewis.
He grew up here.
What about our meeting with Wim?
You'll just have to handle it on your own.
Alright?
I have an appointment with the bank.
I'll first have to hear what they say.
You know it's not going
to help the situation.
Sell me the place, you won't
get another offer like this.
Matewis…
I think the time has come for you
to accept that you're not a farmer.
Is everything okay? I was getting worried.
I'm seated in the passage
Where the sun can sing
It's quiet in the corner and it's cold
Can you see what the wind
And the rain does to me
Sun catcher
I'm asking you nicely
Let it shine for me again
Can I help you carry anything?
Your guitar?
No, it's not necessary, thank you.
Let's go inside.
I thought you might like
to be in your old room.
We just use it as a storeroom.
I think there will be a
few shocked faces in town
when they see how much you resemble him.
Almost as if his ghost
is roaming the streets.
Remember when I took this one?
It was the day I think we all knew.
I don't take photos anymore.
What's more to see?
It's always the same.
Nothing changes.
It would probably help
me if I ever go blind.
But luckily my brother is here.
So finally we will have some excitement.
Matewis is somewhere on the farm.
We had to lay off some people.
So he will probably try to convince
you to help him with a few things.
Thank you.
That I can stay here.
Of course.
I told you so, anytime.
It's good that you came.
I've missed you.
-You were unbelievable!
-Thank you.
There you go. Excuse me.
I'll be back.
Hey, what's wrong?
Aren't you excited?
So now you have everything
you've always wanted.
What I wanted?
I thought it was what we wanted?
Hey, hey, hey, what's going on?
You…
should be proud of me.
Of course, I'm proud.
So what then?
Sometimes I think
you don't really love me.
Did you have to bring that up now?
Hmm?
Can't you… I…
I've just had the biggest
show of my career.
How…
How can you be so selfish?
-Yes, I am selfish.
-Yes.
I'm so sorry Louw, you were unbelievable.
I can see you are so happy.
Now you have everything
you've always wanted.
Nothing!
Typical!
-You know what?
-What?
You will never do it!
I really thought that tonight
would be the perfect night.
-So I…
-Louw! Louw!
I'll… I'll be there now. Hold on a moment.
Karien.
Hi.
I wanted to wake you but I
thought you could do with the rest.
I forgot my phone.
I was afraid you'd try to phone.
Remember Dad never allowed
us to ever touch that cup?
I'm still too afraid to touch it.
Have you eaten? I can make you something.
No. Thank you. I…
I'm just going for a walk.
I can go with you.
Come, come, come boys.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
We don't have the whole day.
Can you lift it?
Louw!
Come and help!
Come help, please! We
still have a lot of work to do.
The guys don't know what they're doing!
Let's go, let's go. Come on. That's it.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Thank you.
Porridge, huh? Porridge.
Thanks. There's something
else I want you to do.
Come.
Sandra, this is a surprise.
-I haven't seen you in a while.
-Sorry, I did knock, but I…
Is Louw here?
Oh, I saw him in town yesterday.
Well, he drove past the school.
He went for a walk.
Hopefully, he doesn't run into Matewis,
else who knows what time he'll be back.
Oh, I brought him something.
Well it's for all of you
but I remember he likes it.
Banana bread.
It was always his favourite.
You are welcome to wait a while.
I'm just clearing up.
No, I must get back.
I have a class just now.
I'll tell Louw you were here.
Okay.
Tell him to pop in when he gets a chance.
The children will be so excited
to see a real musician for a change.
Bye.
It looks like it's all coming back to you.
A few years ago…
we almost lost everything.
See those trees over on that side…
that's where the fire started.
I really feel sorry for that little guy.
His father is Wim Cloete.
Wim thinks he can own this whole town.
He owns the farm next to us
and he has a few other farms.
We…
Marie…
sold a section of the farm to his father.
Oh.
I didn't know.
Nothing is going on there,
just a few dilapidated buildings.
We've been using it for a couple
of years to store some broken stuff.
Marie and I
used to go there and shoot my Dad's gun.
How's my sister doing?
You know her.
She has a heart of gold.
She always makes time for everybody.
She is helping out at
one of the shops in town.
Are you finished?
-Hmm.
-Can we go?
Did you bring my guitar in?
I…
It was outside and I…
Did you go through my clothing?
I just unpacked it.
I thought it might be good if
somebody took care of you.
I am not a child! I don't need
anybody to take care of me!
Would you like me to take it back outside?
I'll add it to my list of a million
things I must do tomorrow.
Is the food ready yet?
It smells amazing.
Yes, you can sit so long.
Leave my stuff alone.
I'm longing for you
For the wind that wraps its arms around me
That's how I'm longing
As the sun and the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass me by
Are you longing for me too?
In the distant land where you live
And are you longing
As the sun and the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass you by
That's how I'm longing
As the sun and the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass me…
Hey!
Sorry, Sir.
I… I didn't know you were there.
No, no, don't worry. I just…
I just got a fright.
I'm Louw.
Was it… Was it you that was singing?
Uh, no… No, Sir.
S… S… Sorry I bothered you.
No, you, you didn't…
Your coach phoned me.
You didn't go to practice again.
Do you want to disappoint me?
Venter, look at your father
when he's talking to you.
And that?
Did you get into a fight again?
N… N… No.
No, Dad.
What have I always told you?
There are only two types
of people in this world.
The hunters and the prey.
The weak ones.
Those who are left behind.
And we…
We are never the prey.
I'll deliver the package if you like.
If through it all, you get the time
please drop that off as well.
Okay, it's fine.
Excuse me… Do you need help, Sir?
Louw!
Louw.
My word! Please to meet you.
Henk.
Marie has told me so much about you.
It's great that you're back in town.
Hopefully, we'll get a
chance to hear you play.
What?
You said he must start playing again.
I… sometimes listen to
your music while I'm working.
Really… it's very deep.
Thank you.
Your ability… gift to capture emotion is,
you know, the heart
and soul of a song, right?
Well, there's a table back
there that needs me, um…
I'll see you tomorrow.
And… Louw.
A pleasure meeting you.
Likewise.
Sometimes I help out at the shop.
Matewis said so, yes.
-Louw, I'm sorry…
-Marie, please it's…
Louw! Marie!
Here you are.
I'm not following you, I promise.
So when are visiting my class? Huh?
I… I don't think…
The children were excited when they heard
the famous Louw van Lier is in town.
I played them some of your songs.
Well, actually, some of them
have already been performed.
I'm sorry. You should know me by now.
I get so carried away.
So how does it feel being back in town?
-Yes, I…
-It must be quite boring?
-He's helping Matewis on the farm.
-Oh, really?
Um… Do you know a…
a child, Wim?
-Wim's son?
-Oh, Venter?
Wim Cloete's son. Yes.
He's in our school.
I mean, he attended
my class once or twice, but…
He just sat there.
I think he was too shy to participate.
Anyways…
Uh, Sandra! I'm late again.
Okay, Louw, it was so good to see you.
Come and visit! Please!
Okay, guys. Bye.
Wow! She has lots of energy.
She could give some to Eskom.
Um, hey, when…
When last did you see Mom?
I go every week.
I don't think she recognises me anymore.
If you catch her on a good day…
She often asks about Dad.
I just say he's somewhere on the farm.
It seems like it makes her happy.
I'll see you back at the farm?
Yes, fine.
Bye.
It's a farm!
There are always good times and bad times.
I need your help.
I've always paid!
How long have I been one of your clients?
P… P… Piggy!
Nice!
Please listen to me, Mrs. Malan.
The world has become green.
Yes.
My dad has pushed the
workers hard the last few years.
He sounds as if he can be quite strict.
D… D…
D… Do…
Do you know…
M… M…
Miss… Naude?
We were friends in high school.
A… A… Are…
Are you going to help in her class?
No.
I don't think so.
H… Her…
Her class…
performed your version of
"I Miss You" last year.
It seems like she really likes that one.
That was unbelievable.
I just needed to tell you that.
Uh.… I um…
I love the way you interpret the songs.
I've never heard "I Miss You"
sound like that.
With so much passion.
The whole audience was enchanted.
-Thank you.
-Karien.
Louw.
I think I have a card here somewhere.
I know most of the club owners.
Give me a call.
I'll arrange something for you.
-Thank you.
-Pleasure.
Karien… Yes.
I…
often listen to your…
music.
I'm sorry to hear that.
So you like heartbreak songs?
I…
I… I like…
to know that I…
to know that I'm not alone.
That…
That there are other people who…
I always thought…
feeling that way would
make me more creative.
But there comes a point where…
where things get too
bad to write about them.
I understand.
Uh, uh, that's m… m… m… my dad.
-I… I have to go…
-It's okay. It's okay.
If you ever need anything,
come and look for me at the farm.
T… Thank you.
Where have you been? Huh?
I told you to wait in the car. Huh?
Get in.
I know you don't think
I'm good enough for you.
But I don't know what more I can do!
I did not want to be a farmer.
I did it for your father… for you!
I… Your whole family!
But everything I do,
it's not good enough for you.
What do you expect when
I find out from the bank
that we might lose our home?
I can't live with so much
uncertainty every day…
What do you want from me?
Don't always run away
to the farm every time
when things get tough or dark or unhappy.
I can't talk to you about this.
-I want to talk to you.
-Leave me alone!
Louw, I didn't realise
you'd be back already.
I only do it when I need to relax.
And don't be worried,
it's only farm issues.
Nothing for you to stress about.
You left this place
behind a long time ago.
Aren't you going to say something?
You're just like Matewis.
Why do you do this?
Even when we were kids,
you'd lock yourself in the room
and I had to get along on my own!
And when you came out you'd
make as if nothing was wrong!
I don't know how Karien survived with you!
And you two?
It seems the only thing that
can keep this farm alive is anger!
The dancer was gone
By midnight the moon was sad and beautiful
And when the new morning
Arose from the mountain
Grey birds were watching us
Forty days and forty nights
We're looking for the mystical farmer
Like the black horses of midnight thoughts
He keeps on his guard and watches
Over his shoulder with a strange grin
And danced in the night
With the moon over his shoulder
With an eye which bravely came closer
To ask me my name
P… P… P… Piggy.
P… P… P… Piggy!
Wow, Piggy,
but you've got some pair of tits.
They're almost bigger than Miss Naude's.
P… P… Piggy.
Should I get you one of
my sisters br….br…. bras?
P… P… Piggy. I'm talking to you.
P… P… Piggy.
Leave me!
-Leave me…
-Geez!
Piggy got himself
a nice pair of balls this holiday.
Hey, hey!
Hey, what's going on?
Hey!
Venter, Venter!
Stop.
Boys.
Out.
Hey! I'm warning you!
Venter?
S… Sorry, Sir…
Pl… Please don't phone my parents.
-P… P… Please…
-Okay, okay, okay.
Who can I call then?
Do you want to talk about it?
Uh… no.
S… S… Sorry that I bothered you.
Not at all.
I'm glad you did.
Did you take music lessons
when you were at school?
-Louw…
-No…
So kind of you to come and visit me.
Well… us.
Hello Venter, it's good to see you again.
Hello, Miss Naude.
Okay, so I told my children
you were going to pop in.
They're so excited to see you.
Yes, bu… uh…
Look if you can bring me the sun
There's a song that the sun can sing
It's quiet in the corner
In the cold season
Can you see what the wind
And the rain does to me
I'm asking you nicely
Let it shine for me again
Well done, guys. Okay.
Continue so long with what
we started working on yesterday
and next time we can ask
Louw a few questions. Okay?
Quiet.
Hey, are you okay?
I can't do this.
Don't stress, they don't bite.
I told you I can't do this!
We need to go.
Louw?
Louw.
Can't you see I'm not ready for this?
Sorry, when I saw you I thought you…
What? Hmm?
What did you think? I was here to see you?
-No, I…
-Don't!
You were always like this.
Leave me alone.
I told you not this one!
Mrs. Malan, let's find the right one.
Philip, tell her to get away from me.
Let's go and sit, Mrs. Malan. Come.
We're just going to sit for a bit.
There you go.
Can you give me the beige jersey, please?
-There you go.
-Thank you.
She never listens to me.
I've told her, this one is my favourite.
Hey.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, Mommy, it's me.
I'm here.
I love looking at this
photo of the two of you.
You look so happy.
Did you bring her with you?
I would love to meet her.
Your dad as well.
Mom, she um…
She really wanted to be here, Mom.
Marie got those CDs for your dad.
What CDs?
I couldn't believe it myself.
I always tell them how famous my son is
but I don't think they believe me.
But I always knew.
You have this inner strength within you.
You always made me so proud.
Mrs. Malan, it's time for your medication.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, my dear.
Don't you want to play something for me?
It's nice to just feel
normal again for a change.
All I get these days
are pitiful looks. As if…
I'm suffering from some terminal illness.
Except Matewis.
I guess he just doesn't know any better.
Karien is dead.
And… I cannot change it.
Nobody can.
And…
I know you blame me for leaving.
And that's okay.
I know you didn't have a choice.
You also had dreams.
Mom needs me here.
I think she would've been in a
much worse condition if I also left.
I went to see her.
I tried not to tell you.
She thought I was Dad.
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I told you, you look alike.
What did she say?
Something about CD's,
that you supposedly bought.
Oh.
Wait here.
Dad asked me to get these
when I came to see you in Pretoria.
He also didn't have a CD player,
so I had to get him that too.
I don't think he ever listened to it.
But just to have it…
meant so much to him.
He wasn't very impressed
that you used Mom's surname.
But I think he understood.
I remember when you came to get them.
I even drew a heart because
I thought it was for you.
If I knew it was for…
What?
That it was for Dad?
You probably wouldn't have given it to me.
No…
probably not.
Marie.
Thank you that you were always
the one who tried to keep us together.
I thought you'd still be at school?
I bunked one of my c… c… classes.
Were you just playing now?
No.
I…
I'm just thinking.
I um…
I know people don't
listen to CDs anymore but…
Miss Naude said you
attended her class a few times?
My dad did not want me to do music.
He never even attended one of my shows.
And I always thought it was
because he was ashamed of me.
And I used it… to drive me.
To prove him wrong.
C… C… Can you play something for me?
I tell you what,
I'll play you something if…
If you sing with me.
No, no.
I understand you're afraid, Venter.
I am also afraid. Always.
My throat becomes dry and…
my heart beats so fast, it
feels like it's going to jump out.
But I've learnt that it's
perhaps a good thing.
It means I'm at the point of…
doing something important.
Do what makes you happy, Venter.
Not what other people want you to do.
I'm longing for you
For the wind that wraps its arms around me
That's how I'm longing
As the sun and the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass me by
Are you longing for me too?
In the distant land where you live now
And are you longing
As the sun and the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass you by
I'm longing for you
I long because I really like you
I am longing as the sun
And the moon and the wind
And the clouds pass you by
Blow wind
Bring him back to me
-Blow wind
-And the clouds pass me by
Bring him back to me
I'm longing for you
For the wind that wraps its arms around…
Are you okay?
Venter, I know how difficult it is
to love somebody who hurts you.
It feels as if you shouldn't love them.
And sometimes we mustn't.
Come in… Hey, come in.
-Hi. Do you have a moment?
-Yes.
I'm just marking.
And I'm done!
Don't worry, it's just a short exercise.
It doesn't count towards their final mark.
I…
I came to apologise for the other day.
-Louw, it's…
-I know you're trying to be friendly.
So I'm…
I'm sorry.
I know I can sometimes
come across a bit too strong.
I think that's why you broke up with me
in the first place.
N… No. It…
It wasn't that, I…
I don't know. At that stage…
I thought I wasn't good enough.
I needed to find my own feet, you know.
And it…
didn't feel fair to drag somebody
with me into the unknown.
-And look where I ended up!
-Hmm.
I see you're still fascinated by France.
And Asia.
Did you ever go?
No, no. Those are just gifts.
I'm lucky if I get the chance
to leave the province.
-I was there a few years ago.
-Paris?
-To perform?
-No. No. I…
Karien and I went.
France, Germany, Holland.
Wow.
I think you'd love it.
Was it easy for you
to leave here at the time?
No, it's never easy to
leave everything behind.
Family, friends and you
know how my father was.
I don't know, I…
My dreams weren't here.
I had this…
unbelievable desire to…
I don't know?
I think I would have gone crazy if
I had to stay here a moment longer.
Yes.
A few years ago I bought a backpack.
Way too big for me.
A place for everything, secret pockets.
You know, the whole nine yards.
I had to make sure that there was
enough space in case I needed it.
And then I put it next to my front door
so it would always remind me that
one day I would see the world.
The children kept asking me:
"Ma'am, when are you going on your trip?"
And I always had an excuse.
I had to organise a school function or
there was a sick family member.
I eventually became so tired of it,
I hid it in the back of my cupboard.
Well, if your offer still stands…
I'd like to help in the class.
But let's first give it a
try and see how it goes.
Of course.
The children are crazy about you.
They keep asking me
when you're coming back.
I want, I want to see if
Venter doesn't maybe…
We can go and see if you want to.
Oh, wow!
And that unbelievable music.
Have they done productions of them?
Haven't gone that big yet.
-Hi, Venter.
-Did you play well?
Yes.
I take it he wasn't very happy
with some of the decisions.
No.
So, Louw's coming to help
us with the music class--
Come, Venter, we're leaving.
Yes, Dad.
-See you on the farm.
-Bye.
Hi, I'm Louw.
That's right. The singer?
My wife says you were
quite famous, in your day.
Louw's going to help
out in the music class.
Maybe Venter can join us?
How do you know my son?
Oh, from the farm.
We chatted a bit while you were
talking to my brother-in-law.
Yes, well maybe you can talk some
sense into him to accept my offer.
Venter, we're leaving.
Yes Dad.
Not the most pleasant man, is he?
No.
I'm late!
Morning.
Hey.
What a handsome brother I have.
I thought I'd try to make a good
first impression in front of the children.
Well, um, second impression.
We can drive together if you'd like.
I'm working at the shop today
and I'm sure Sandra
won't mind dropping you off.
No, it's fine, thank you.
Oh, damn, I must go.
Not that Henk minds if I'm late but still.
-See you tonight.
-Yes.
-Bye.
Bye, Matewis.
Matewis.
Welcome to voicemail.
You have one new message.
Hi Marie.
I'm just making sure
you're still coming in today.
I'm waiting with bated breath.
I'll see you shortly.
To repeat this message, press one.
Blow wind
Nice.
Bring him back to me
Blow wind
That was…
beautiful.
I couldn't have done it better myself.
Fantastic.
You see, coming from a real musician.
Okay. Let's show him what
we've practised for the festival.
-Be good. See you.
-Bye.
There you go. Bye.
Bye.
You've always had such beautiful hands.
So, um…
What are you still
planning for the festival?
Oh, still a few songs.
We must open with the National Anthem.
After that,
I thought we could do "Sun Catcher".
And then we must decide which
other songs we are going to do.
I was wondering if Venter
doesn't want to sing something.
If it's okay with you?
Yes, of course.
Yes, I think he, he needs it.
You know, if my dad…
Excuse me.
Venter, can I have a quick word with you?
Hey, P…P…P…Piggy!
Venter, at the festival,
I thought it would be a great
opportunity for you to show your talent.
Miss Naude said you can take part.
My d… dad said I'm not
supposed to speak to you.
Venter, your voice, it's…
It's really something special.
I, I…
I must g… go.
Leave me alone.
You have a talent, Venter.
And it would be a shame
if you allow your dad to…
And what about you? Huh?
You say I mustn't waste my talent.
But what about yours?
My dad says you only came back
because you made an
ass of yourself in Pretoria.
-I'm sorry.
-Your dad is right.
I did make an idiot of myself.
But it's no excuse for what he's doing.
You deserve better, Venter.
You must believe it.
I…
I must go.
Venter.
Sorry, where did you say Matewis is?
A meeting with our accountant.
He didn't tell me why.
So, how's it going at the school?
I'm sure the children love it.
And Sandra probably
hasn't felt this good in a while.
It went well.
Stressful, but good.
I…
spoke to Venter, but he…
Well his, his dad is…
Remember the time when you
entered the school's talent festival?
You knew you'd win but you only
wanted to see how upset Dad would be.
Yes.
It's not easy for everybody
to leave the known behind.
Especially not the people around here.
But you're different.
You'll never be someone who fits in a box.
And
as much as I enjoy having you here.
It breaks my heart to see you like this.
I saw your lyrics.
Not on purpose. It fell.
You wrote her a song.
I was busy writing it but I…
I couldn't finish it.
I…
I never knew why.
But…
today when…
when I saw the children sing.
The innocent joy on their faces.
There was no guard.
They didn't pretend to be something else.
Then I realised…
what a liar I am.
I loved Karien.
She made me feel it was…
worthwhile leaving everything behind,
my friends and my family.
But there was always something.
Something that stopped
me from telling her.
As if it would make me weak…
or give her too much power over me.
And I slowly began pushing her away.
I focused all my
energy on my music and…
to prove Dad wrong.
I never told her how much I loved her.
She never got the
opportunity to give this to me.
She got so tired of waiting for me that…
that she wanted to do it herself.
Louw…
You must stop blaming yourself.
She knew that you loved her.
Not the way I wanted her to know.
And do you know how it feels to…
always think that people must
lower their expectations to be with you.
Every day of my life.
Matewis always wanted a big family.
Me too.
But when we found out that
I couldn't have children…
I could see how disappointed he was.
He said he feels sorry for me but…
I know he wishes I was somebody else.
I think he even blames me
for the farm's barren land.
The drought.
As if I contaminated the entire farm.
I am so sorry, Marie.
I can see it on his face.
How he thinks…
about what his life could have been.
It's easy to think about…
what could have happened if
you made other choices in your life.
I see what you're like
when you're with Henk.
No, no it's beautiful. You…
You even look different.
Like the sister I knew.
Happy.
Do you think um…
Do you think Matewis suspects anything?
I don't think so.
Henk said…
It's probably nothing.
But I forgot my phone here
today and Henk left a message
and I didn't get it.
-But you don't think he, he would…
-No.
No, in any case, Henk
only asked where I was and,
and there's nothing to tell, it's…
We didn't do anything. It's just innocent.
It's just nice to feel like…
somebody is treating
me like something new.
I think Matewis thinks I am
a broken piece of equipment.
Probably means I belong with the
rest of the broken things on this farm.
Can we have a word, please?
I better go and check if he is okay.
It's okay.
I haven't h… heard this s… song before.
I'm still trying to finish it.
It's still very rough.
I didn't think I'd see you again.
I… wanted to c… come
and a… apologise, Sir.
You've got nothing to apologise for.
You sounded like the voice in my head.
And it's good that you spoke for yourself.
I… I don't care.
I was wrong.
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
Now I'm standing in shame
This is my burden
Do you want to sing it with me?
I… can't.
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
So I'm standing in shame
This is my burden
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
I keep stumbling again and again
With prayers at night
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
So I'm standing in shame
This is my burden
I wish I was a better man
Like you deserved
I'm stumbling again and again.
There you go. Here.
-If you want to practise.
-Thank you.
Don't worry, I'll explain.
It's okay.
-Venter, get in the car.
-Wim, relax, please.
This is what you enjoy.
To be alone with young boys.
Dad!
You're such a wuss.
No wonder you admire him.
Wim please, we were just writing music.
Is this what you want?
To come from a family
that everybody laughs at.
-On a farm where nothing grows?
-Yes.
My family is not perfect.
And we don't pretend to be.
That's all I've seen since I've been here.
People who run away from the truth.
You should've heard how
your father spoke about you.
How ashamed he was of you.
And me of him.
I didn't even want his name.
Well fortunately for him
he had two children like you.
Because between you
and your infertile sister
there'll be nothing left of his name.
No!
-Louw!
-Don't touch him!
Venter!
No. No!
Venter, get in the car!
I'm sorry I wasn't here when…
I… don't think you wanted
me here in any way.
It probably worked
out best for both of us.
You've always been with me.
In the back of my mind.
Busy telling me that
I'm not going to make it.
The… anger that it provoked in me.
I used it…
to drive myself.
So that I could come back one day
and show you what I have achieved.
And now…
Now I am exactly what you said I'd be.
A failure.
Not worthy of the Malan name.
My mother's son.
Not yours.
Marie is struggling, Dad.
She hides it well but I can see it.
I always thought she was the strong one.
Like you.
She was the only one who
could stand up to you.
She showed me the CDs she got for you.
Hell, Dad, why couldn't you
just once say something positive?
Just once.
Mom did it so many, so many times
that it started feeling normal.
But if something like that
could've come from you.
Do you know what it would've meant to me?
I wish you could have met Karien.
Maybe then…
you would've understood what I was doing.
That I made the right choice back then.
She always said what she was thinking.
Not like us.
Maybe then I would've
been able to tell you everything
while you could still hear me.
Before you became just
another voice in the wind.
But I think it's time I realise that…
me being here is not good for anybody.
It only serves as a…
memory that you cannot
run away from yourself,
no matter how hard you try.
But um…
There's this boy.
He reminds me a lot of myself.
I want to tell him to run.
To run and never turn back.
What example am I for him?
And his dad is…
Let's just say, it makes me
think you were never that bad.
Things could've been worse.
Marie.
Hey.
It's Matewis.
It's okay.
What happened?
You're bleeding…
Let it go. It doesn't matter.
What happened?
It's all my fault.
Hey.
I'm going to tell Matewis about Henk.
I'm sure he already knows but…
I just feel everything must just come out.
I don't want any more secrets.
It was just nice to…
to feel loved again.
That's something one
should never turn away.
I'm going to try and get some sleep.
I can't believe he hit you.
-And now, this thing with Matewis.
-Yes.
Marie is going to visit
him again tomorrow.
See if he can come home.
Is there anything else I can get you?
Tell me about your trip.
Where did you want to go to?
Well, a few years ago I
saw a photo of a temple.
The Tiger's Nest in Bhutan.
It's built on the edge of a mountain.
Almost as if it was there first and
the mountain appeared around it later.
Come sit here.
Anyway, um…
so…
I remember just staring at the photo and
I wondered how it must feel
to stand in such a holy place
and peek over the edge.
You know, just to feel the
foundation that you are standing on
which has been there for centuries and
it could slip away at any time.
I suspected something.
When I heard his voice message…
it clarified everything.
I wanted to confront him.
I even thought of…
But then I remembered your face.
Joyful. Happy.
Something you're not when you're with me.
I've never really felt
that I make you happy.
And I think your dad
also didn't think I could.
That's how I always feel around you.
As if you blame me because I can't…
You're everything in my life.
And just the idea of losing you.
Can I come in?
-Hi.
How did you handle it…
when you lost Karien?
First, I decided that my
life had ended right there.
That I also died.
I didn't go to Heaven or,
or Hell, I was just there.
As if something from outside
was controlling my body.
And…
it took me a long time…
to…
remember what it felt like to be happy.
And…
when I sit amongst all
the rubble on the farm…
and I look at all the broken and
rusted things that
people have thrown away.
Then I realised that everything,
once upon a time, was loved.
Or at least useful.
And I could see myself there.
And it made me think…
why I'm still here.
If I can't make people laugh or…
cry or
even feel?
Matewis…
there is only the present.
There's only the pain and…
the joy and the sorrow of the
past that must be left behind.
What we do now means something.
This is how we change our world.
I want to make your sister happy.
I know I'm the reason you are so unhappy.
I think it's time to sell the farm.
It's not making any of us happy.
It's the best thing to do.
Long afloat on shipless oceans
Gave everything just to smile
Until your seeing eyes and fingers
Drew me to your island
Stop. Stop. Stop.
And you sang
It's perfect.
Sail to me
Sail to me, let my arms enfold you
Here I am
I'm waiting to hold you
I'm so confused like the newly born child
So plagued like the tide
Must I stand in the middle of the waves
Or will I go and lie next to the dead
My bride
I'm waiting to hold you
Sail to me
Look, I think we'll take
Witteberg this year.
-Absolutely.
-For sure.
Good afternoon gents.
-Good afternoon.
-How are you doing?
-Good.
-Ah, that's good.
We have a good team this year.
Yes, yes, yes.
Pity that Venter couldn't play.
Yes.
Freak accident, you say?
Yes. The child has a
habit of hurting himself.
Mr. Cloete.
Venter is a good boy.
He just needs the right
kind of encouragement.
You'll see. He's stronger than he looks.
Well…
I'll see you guys at the concert, right?
-Yeah.
-Yes, yes.
Listen can you tell me
why he is our coach.
Because he looks much more eager
to hear songs being
sung than to win the game.
-How you feeling?
-Okay.
I'm nervous.
It's going to be wonderful.
Have you seen Venter?
No.
Not since the whole…
Yeah.
I'm sure he is okay.
Just children of the wind
The next song is one that I wrote
as a tribute to somebody very special.
And I wish I could have
said it before it was too late.
So I hope it helps somebody here
to not make the same mistake.
The fucking man can't sing.
His being is crushed.
Watch him. He thinks he's big.
Listen.
Let's show them who's the better man.
This is my confession
My soul laid bare
A call to those who left me
Before I could say my say
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
So I'm standing in shame
This is my burden
I wish I was a better man
Which you deserved
I stumble again and again
With prayers in the wind
But my road is not finished yet
My time is not yet over
And before I go to the depths
There are still thoughts in my head
That I would meet you again
And my life has purpose
I promise you, my love
All of it that I still have
I wish I was a better man
One that you deserved
So I'm standing in shame
This is my burden
I wish I was a better man
Like you deserved
I stumble again and again
Prayers in the wind
-That was wonderful.
-Thank you.
-That song was wonderful.
-Matewis.
-Congrats your show was unbelievable.
I didn't think that you
could sing like that.
So.
It looks like you two
were the heroes tonight.
W… w…w…w…
Wh… w…
When I stood on that stage
and saw you standing there alone,
angry at the whole world,
while everybody was so happy.
For the first time I realised
that I am better than you, Dad.
And I am also better off than you, Dad.
I just feel sorry for you, Dad.
That you lost so much in life.
Yes, drive safely.
Go well.
And, what did they say?
Well, they are not going
to bully me anymore.
Hopefully.
That's good.
So….
-I see you have a new guitar.
-Yes…
Not as nice as the other one.
-I'm on my way. See you tomorrow.
-Bye.
Have a good evening.
-What did he have to say?
-Oh, nothing.
Thank you.
For what?
That you…
helped me find what I thought…
was lost forever.
Of course.
Come.