♪♪
[plane propeller whirring]
[loud thud]
[crow cawing]
[approaching footsteps]
♪♪
["One of the Boys"
by AamityMae playing]
["One of the Boys" continues]
Lookin' good, Sarah.
You make that
look too easy.
Thanks, Chad. Hey,
I got somethin' for you.
No shit!
This got ripped
off my helmet
on a skydive yesterday.
And survived!
I just found it
in the landing area.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks.
That was a pretty
sick landing, Sarah.
Thanks.
- Did you enjoy your solo?
- I did.
You know, you'd have
a lot more fun
jumping with us.
So you keep telling me.
Just 'cause you're
the new girl
doesn't mean
you can't make friends.
You should come out
with us some time.
Is that
your way of asking?
Well, yeah,
I'm not not-asking.
[chuckles] Wow,
I can't say I've ever
heard that line before.
You're not gonna make
this easy on me.
Where's the fun in that?
- You mind if I leave this
here for Kris?
- Yeah, no doubt.
[Chad]
That was classic.
I've never seen Payson
get shut down before.
I don't think it's ever
happened, to be honest.
[scoffs] Just another
cocky Skygod.
Every drop zone has one.
You done
with that packing weight?
Um, yup.
Who was that?
That's Kris.
He's been packing
parachutes
a long time.
- Does he jump?
- Used to.
They say he was
pretty bad-ass
back in the day.
Guess he decided to quit
while he was ahead.
[P.A.] Load 5, gear up.
You're on five-minute call.
Load 5.
Dude, give it up.
It's never gonna happen.
I'm with Wade.
She's never gonna
come around.
You've been trying
to get her to jump with us
since she got here.
What's so special
about her, anyway?
You don't know
who that is?
Skydiving runs
in that girl's blood.
We need a sixth, Lisa.
And she's the one.
Whatever.
["Runnin' Wild"
by Andrea Vasquez playing]
- [gasps] Payson!
- Sorry, sorry.
- I have
a confession to make.
- Oh?
Since when do they
allow women
into the priesthood?
I need something from you.
I just know talent
when I see it,
and right now,
the team could use you.
You ever heard of the phrase,
"I don't want to belong
to any club
that would have me
as a member?"
Yeah, Groucho Marx.
You get points
for knowing that.
Doesn't change the fact
that I like to jump alone.
[plane flying overhead]
Jumping alone is
kind of like masturbating.
It'll do in a pinch,
but it's kinda depressing.
Maybe you don't
masturbate right.
[car engine starts]
Mm-hmm?
A group of us are going
to church later.
You ever been?
What self-respecting girl
hasn't been to church
a few times?
So I'll see you there?
I'll say... maybe.
[horn honks]
They missed you.
[quacking]
They're just ducks, Mom.
They don't miss me.
[quacking continues]
You like it?
It's a new blend
I've been working on.
Yeah.
It's like a mix
between tree bark
and peat moss.
It's healthy.
Just drink it.
It's good
to have you back.
to be back...
I think.
I was hoping
we could fix things.
I would like that.
Look, before you left,
I let my emotions
get the best of me.
I was angry.
I hope you can
understand that.
Are you still jumping?
We're talking
about fixing things,
and that's where
you want to go?
I'm staying safe,
Mom, don't worry.
What I worry about
is you moving
from place to place,
all by yourself.
You don't stick around
in one place long enough
to make any friends.
I got invited to hang out
with some people tonight.
Well, good.
I hope you're gonna go.
I haven't decided.
Sarah...
you should go.
You need it.
♪♪
- [Payson] There she is.
- [cheering]
Ah, shit.
Thanks a lot.
Guess that means
I'm going first.
Nice to meet you, too.
That's Greg. He bet me
you wouldn't show.
[Evan]
I think he's got
a little crush.
That's Evan.
- Yo.
- Hey.
- Wade, Lisa.
- 'Sup.
What is she
doing here?
Come on, Lisa,
church is for everyone.
Yeah, I still don't get
why they call this church.
'Cause this is where you go
to pray for your life.
- [Sarah laughs]
- [Wade] Damn, dude,
that's dark.
[Greg] Welcome
to church, Sarah.
- Yeah!
- [Evan] Whoo!
He cheats death again.
Whoo-whoo.
So, uh, I hear
you might be joining us
for some formation jumps
tomorrow.
I don't know about that.
I've never done
any formation jumps before.
[Wade] What?
What do you do
when you skydive?
What, do you just play
"Princess of the Sky"
- up there all by yourself?
- [laughs]
I guess I've just always
kept to myself.
I like it that way.
I wonder if other people
like it that way, too.
So, listen, uh,
now that we finally
have six people...
I think we should
try "The Hex."
[Greg]
You guys gonna jump
or what?
That seems like a bad idea,
but what do I know?
Let's go, Wade.
See ya.
[Lisa]
Bombs away.
Whoo!
Go, go, go!
[screams]
- Ooo! [screams]
- [Lisa] Hurry up
and land, Wade.
[Wade]
Coming in hot, Lisa.
♪♪
So, hey...
- The Hex?
- Yeah.
For real?
I mean, come on.
I'd expect this
from Wade, but not you.
It's just--
I mean, we've all
heard the stories.
I mean, you believe every story
you hear at the drop zone?
Hey, trust me.
Have I ever
steered you wrong?
Okay.
♪♪
Have a good jump, Sarah.
Thanks.
Whoo.
Whoo!
Listen, I didn't mean
to assume anything.
I know you haven't agreed
to jump with us.
And I'm sorry I said
jumping alone was lame.
Uh, it's okay.
I'm sorry I questioned
your masturbating skills.
[laughs]
So, what's the Hex?
It's this jump
I've always wanted to do,
but you need six people.
- Six talented people.
- Ah.
What do you say?
See you in the morning.
Whoo.
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Evan] This jump? It's true,
you need six people.
But the reason
it's called the Hex
is a couple of people
have died trying it.
Seriously?
[Greg] That's
just an urban legend.
Nobody's ever died
doing the Hex.
We can do something else
if you're uncomfortable, Sarah.
You could just film us.
I'm not much
of a bystander, Lisa.
Thanks, though.
That's what I'm talking about!
No, not the white board!
I hate
the white board.
Yes, Wade. I know you do,
and I thought you might
have a hard time
visualizing
this particular jump.
So here...
I made this just for you.
- [chuckles]
- Ooh.
- [Wade] Really?
- We fly like this,
and on my key...
- Key... huh?
- [Wade laughs]
- [Sarah laughs]
- Hardy-fucking-har.
[laughing]
Fuck me, this actually
does help, though.
Just try not to...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, baby.
Oh, no, don't do it.
♪♪
Remember, a collision
at these speeds
can knock you out cold.
Err on the side of caution.
We all have to die.
[all] But we don't have
to die today!
[trumpets]
That's right,
smart asses. Gear up.
Looks like your altimeter's
sticking.
Yeah, it does that
sometimes.
It's all right.
My eyes can be my altimeter.
I really don't think Sarah
should be center.
It's her first time doing
any kind of formation,
and you're putting her right
in the most dangerous slot.
She'll be fine.
Try thinking
with your other head?
If anything happens to her,
it's gonna be your fault.
Um, hi, guys.
You know, I'm sitting
right here.
Don't let her rattle you.
Lisa can be a little
overdramatic at times.
Eat a dick, Greg.
You'll be great.
Yeah, and if you really
want to be great,
you can flash
the pilot your boobs,
and he'll give us
some extra altitude!
In your dreams.
[laughing]
All right,
everybody on comms!
- Let's do this!
- [Wade] Aw, yeah.
Hey, Payson, what's
the capital of Thailand?
What?
- Bang Cock!
- [Wade laughs]
Never gets old.
Ow, fucker. Just get
in the damn door, Evan.
[Wade]
Let's get it on.
["My Enemies" playing]
[Wade]
Ready, set, go!
[song continues]
[Wade]
Nice and easy, Sarah.
[Sarah]
Nice and easy yourself.
I am in my slot.
[Payson]
Okay, looking good,
everybody.
Watch your levels.
Ready... and...
key!
[Sarah]
Oh, shit,
I'm losing it.
[Wade] Whoa, whoa,
whoa! Fuck! Shit!
[Lisa]
What the hell?!
[Evan] Well, guys,
that sucked.
[Payson] Break off.
Break off.
♪♪
[Payson]
Everybody good?
- [Greg] Greg's fine.
- [Evan] Roger.
- [Wade] Go for Wade.
- [Sarah] Sarah's good.
[Lisa]
Is she, though?
[Payson] All right,
see you guys on the ground.
♪♪
Whoo.
[all whooping, laughing]
[overlapping conversation]
How'd it go?
Good enough.
We can do better,
though.
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
[Lisa] Here she comes.
She's coming. She's coming.
Sorry about that, guys.
My foot clipped Wade's head,
and I-I kinda bugged out.
Hey, hey, no sweat.
I got somethin' for ya.
Homie hat!
[all whooping]
Ah, don't worry about it.
It's like a skydiving
dunce cap.
- [Lisa] Yeah, it is.
- We've all been there.
- [Wade] Looks good on her.
- Was that seriously
your first formation?
Why, so you can make
a bunch of virgin jokes?
I told you that
last night.
[scoffs] No, because
if it really
was your first time,
then that means...
- Sarah's buying!
- [cheering]
["Girls Night Out"
by Andrea Vasquez playing]
So, are you stoked
on that jump or what?
Yes.
I mean, it-it does suck
that I messed it up,
but... [sighs]
maybe I shouldn't expect
much on my first try.
Nah, don't even sweat it.
This crew's been jumping
together a while now.
If I had a dollar
for every jump
that I fucked up,
I could pay
for this beer...
- [message alert dings]
- ...and some pizza.
- Who's that?
- My mother.
If she knows
I've been out jumping
and hasn't heard from me
by sunset,
she tends
to assume the worst.
Why's that?
Did you have
a friend go in
or something?
Something like that.
Somebody close to you?
Yeah.
Is that why
you jump alone?
That's part of it.
I've only been jumping
a couple of years.
I never had a friend
die skydiving.
You will.
Eventually, we all do.
[exhales sharply]
["We Own the Night"
by Jenezen playing]
All right, guys.
Now listen up.
Hang on. Wait a second.
All right, so I want to run
the Hex again tomorrow.
This time,
with no mistakes.
I think we can all agree
that we put a little
too much stress on Sarah
by putting her in the middle.
I think we can also agree
that somebody already tried
to tell you that.
Which is why
I'm going to be
taking the center.
- [Evan] Whoo!
- Sarah...
You'll be right here
across from me.
Evan...
you're right here.
Greg...
you'll be right here
between Lisa and Wade.
Guys, if this was easy,
everyone would do it.
Get some rest,
and I'll see you
at the ass-crack of dawn.
[Evan] All right,
see you, Payson.
["We Own the Night" continues]
Whatever. Wade,
come on, let's go.
I guess we're leaving.
I'm riding with you.
I'm out, bro.
Lisa, wait up.
She loves me.
Don't take it
too personally.
Lisa's just jealous.
And she doesn't have
a terribly high emotional IQ.
That's stupid.
She's just as good
a skydiver as I am.
[light chuckle]
Not that. Payson.
Are they a thing?
Used to be. Lisa still
wants them to be.
But that was never
gonna work out.
They don't seem
exactly compatible.
[laughs]
She's fucking crazy!
Oh, good.
You take the bad
with the good, I guess.
She deals with enough
of our shit,
that's for sure.
See ya dark and early.
♪♪
Hey. You want a beer?
Much obliged.
[beer bottle opens]
I saw you guys
tried the Hex today.
Yeah, but I fucked it up.
Obviously.
No shame in that.
The Hex is
a tough formation.
Maybe a handful
of people in the world
that could pull it off.
Have you seen it done?
I have.
Trying it again tomorrow.
Wow!
Good luck.
Thanks.
♪♪
[indistinct announcement on PA]
Do you know how bad
those things are for you?
Yeah, well, we're all
gonna croak sometime.
Yeah, but taurine overdose
seems like a pretty
stupid reason.
Yeah, well, you die
your way, cupcake.
I'll die mine.
["Music"
by Assaf Ayalon playing]
[shouting] All right,
skydive! Whoo!
Oh! [laughs]
How's it going, Jerry?
Payson!
How you doing, man?
Not quite as well as you,
by the looks of things.
And what's your name?
Her name's Ingrid.
Only speaks
a few words of English.
Ingrid, huh?
You lucky bastard.
Come on, let's load up.
["Music" continues]
[Andy]
Good morning, L.A. center,
jump 2 is lighting up.
We'll be climbing
at 12,000 feet this mornin'.
Appreciate any advisories.
[control tower] Jump 2, L.A.
center, good morning.
Advise when you're wheels up.
Expect clear skies
from one to two thousand.
Be advised moderate
to severe turbulence reported
all the way to 15,000 feet.
Buckle up, jump 2.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
[Andy]
Copy that. We're rolling.
♪♪
[Wade]
Hey, Jer,
what about getting
a little extra altitude, huh?
I'm not askin' her.
Hey, Ingrid, do you want
the plane to go higher?
Yeah, Ingrid,
have a longer skydive?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
All you have to do is....
Show the boobs
to the pilot,
and he'll take us up
an extra thousand feet.
I-I wouldn't lie to you.
[Payson]
Yo, Andy!
Ingrid wants
to show you something!
[boys shouting]
[laughs]
Sorry about that, folks!
I think the man upstairs
gave us some turbulence
just to make those beautiful
titties bounce!
I'd say that's definitely
worth some extra altitude!
[cheering]
What'd I miss?
♪♪
[alert beeping]
Crouch down for me.
Here we go!
Ready, steady, go!
♪♪
[Payson]
All right, guys.
Here we go.
Ready, set, go!
♪♪
[Payson]
All right, guys,
here we go.
Ready... key!
And key!
Come on, guys, you got it.
Come on, don't let go.
[Lisa]
Holy shit, we did it.
[Payson]
Yeah.
[cheering]
[Payson] Yeah, you!
Ha-ha! All right!
[Sarah]
Yeah! Whoo!
[Payson] That's what I'm
talking about!
Yeah! Awesome!
We got it guys!
- [Sarah] Holy shit,
that was bad-ass.
- [whooping]
[Payson] Good job, guys.
Good shit.
[Greg] What the fuck
just happened?
- [Evan] Did I just
fucking see that?
- [Lisa] Oh, my God!
-  [Evan] What the fuck, man?
- [Lisa] Does anyone see him?
[Wade] We gotta go.
We gotta go. Break off!
♪♪
[Lisa] Evan, do you
see him anywhere?
[Sarah] I don't see
his parachute.
[Evan]
I don't see him.
♪♪
- [Greg] Where's Payson?
- [Wade] I don't know.
- [Greg] Where the hell is he?
- [Wade] He's gone.
All of a sudden,
he was just gone!
[Lisa]
Guys, guys.
It was like he was there
one second, and then
he wasn't.
He must have pulled early.
If he pulled early,
we'd be able to see
his canopy.
Unless it didn't open.
- Disappeared?
- [Lisa] Yeah.
Bill, I know
how this sounds,
but I saw what I saw.
Guys, I've owned
this drop zone
for 22 years.
Nobody has ever
just disappeared.
- [overlapping statements]
- But that's what happened.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll grab a bunch of people.
We'll get them out
in their cars
searching for him.
We'll find him
on the side of the road
packing his parachute.
Somebody should call
the cops, or the paramedics
or whatever.
Man, we don't even know
if he's injured.
He could be stuck
in a tree somewhere
or landed
in someone's backyard.
Right. I can drive.
I can help look.
- I'll go with you.
- [Bill] All right, let's go.
It's just--
I consider myself
a rational person,
and I'm having
a really hard time with this.
I mean, what did you see?
I saw what you saw.
I guess it's possible
he could have just...
I don't know,
had some sort
of canopy malfunction
and had to cut away.
I just feel like one of us
would have seen something.
That's my worst nightmare.
Having to cut away.
- You never had to?
- Nope.
Not that big
of a deal, really.
I mean, when it happens,
it's like time slows way down.
You know what I mean?
And then you just...
Pull your cut-away handle
to lose the mess,
pull your reserve handle
to save your life.
Everyone has to do it,
sooner or later.
There's a part of me
that just wishes
it would happen.
Then maybe it wouldn't
scare me so much.
It wakes me up at night.
My canopy malfunctions,
and for whatever reason,
I can't control it.
I can't cut away.
I used to have
dreams like that.
Used to?
Now I have nightmares
we're about to crash.
I'm stuck inside the plane
and can't get out the door.
Hey, stop here.
♪♪
[birds chirping]
If we don't find him soon,
the chances of finding him
at all are gonna be
pretty slim.
Damn it, Payson.
Where the hell are you?
Come on.
♪♪
[Andy] We covered
as much as we could.
There's no sign of him.
All right, copy that.
Andy circled with a spotter
'til it got dark.
They didn't see anything.
- And the cops?
- Nothin'.
They're waiting inside.
Sarah, they want
to talk to you.
Yeah, that's, uh,
pretty much what I heard
from everyone else.
Now, I have to ask.
Did any of you partake
in any controlled substances
when you went up?
We weren't high,
if that's what you're asking.
Okay. Well, maybe it was
an alien abduction.
Maybe a UFO swooped in
and scooped him up
with a tractor beam.
You think this is funny?
Not at all.
He could be dead or--
or dying out there
somewhere,
and you're sitting here
cracking jokes?
Maybe.
Or maybe...
I don't know, he's sipping
Mai Tais in Palm Springs.
What do you think?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Look at the video!
Oh, I have them all
right here.
How about this video?
- This one?
- [cursor clicks]
What about this one?
Your friend's not
on any of these videos.
He may very well be missing.
But something
about your story's
not checking out.
♪♪
[door closes]
[message alert dings]
[phone chimes]
♪♪
[male voice whispering]
Get up.
[glass clattering]
[dog barking]
[scoffs]
Another point for me.
I shut her down again.
[thud]
[owl hooting]
♪♪
Oh!
[urinating]
Payson?
Jesus fucking Christ!
Payson, what the--
[screams] Get up!
♪♪
What the fuck?
[breathing heavily]
♪♪
[gasps, pants]
Shit!
[loud clatter]
♪♪
[faint voices echoing]
[whisper echoes] Hurry.
[loud thud]
♪♪
[electricity sparking]
[oven hissing]
[door creaks and bangs shut]
Open the door.
Payson! Oh, my God!
[softly] Payson.
[crickets chirping]
♪♪
That's the dumbest story
I ever heard.
You had a bad dream
last night
because of what happened
yesterday.
That's it.
I didn't sleep great
last night either.
This is more
than just a bad dream, Lisa.
Show her.
This is Payson's, isn't it?
Just found it
on the ground last night.
What the fuck, Wade?
How do you have
his altimeter?
I don't know.
I'm pretty sure he had it
on the jump yesterday.
Yeah, he definitely
had it.
I remember because I noticed
it was sticking the other day.
It was stuck on zero.
[Lisa] Well, you guys jump
if you want to. I'm out of here.
She's fine.
She'll be back tomorrow.
[Sarah] What do you think, Evan?
You've been pretty quiet.
[Evan] Payson.
Do we think he's dead?
And if he is,
who did you guys
see last night?
All right, look.
We still don't know
what happened to Payson.
But whatever happened,
he's not haunting us.
♪♪
I didn't think you guys
would make it in today.
Well, we're all
about getting back
on the horse.
- [Andy] All right.
Be safe out there.
- [Greg] Will do.
[plane engine humming]
It's our own fault,
you know?
- For trying the Hex.
- Come on, a cursed skydive?
Are you kidding me?
It wasn't the formation,
and we don't even know
for sure Payson's even dead.
I'm sure. I saw him
last night, too.
Only he said something to me.
What'd he say,
dude?
He said,
"You're next, Evan."
Like next, next?
Guys, okay. May-maybe
Lisa's right.
We're probably just suffering
from some sort of post-traumatic
stress or something.
♪♪
[buzzer rings]
You guys want
to make a plan or what?
No. I'm doing a solo.
Think you can catch me?
With one arm tied
behind my back.
I'll even give you
a head start.
♪♪
Oh, come on, Evan.
You got to make me work
for it a little bit.
Evan?
Come on, Evan,
stop playing around.
Evan?
This isn't funny.
Evan! Oh, my God!
Evan!
Come on!
[screams] Come on, Evan!
♪♪
No! Shit!
Evan!
Evan, I'm gonna
jump you out.
Come on, wake up.
Come on, wake up!
Come on!
Evan, you've got to fly
your parachute.
Evan, can you hear me?
Come on, Evan,
you've got to wake up.
♪♪
[gasps]
[thud]
Evan!
Oh, God, Evan!
Oh!
Shit!
Guys, help!
- [Greg] Sarah!
- [Wade] What happened?
- Is he okay?
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Fuck! Help!
[screams]
Oh, my God!
What the fuck?!
[Greg] Hey! Evan! Hey, hey!
[Sarah breathing heavily]
His heart
isn't beating. Evan!
Oh, man, this is bad.
Holy shit.
He's not breathing.
- Dude, he's not breathing.
- [Sarah] Evan!
[crying]
♪♪
Wade went to tell Lisa
what happened.
You did everything
you could.
The paramedics said
it was cardiac arrest.
He was probably dead
before he even hit
the ground.
Cardiac arrest?
Doesn't sound
very likely, does it?
How long have you
been jumping, Greg?
About five
or six years. Why?
And have you ever heard
of anything like this
happening before?
To someone his age?
No.
["There Goes the Devil"
by Michael Shynes playing]
Is this who I think it is?
That's me and my Dad.
That's the last picture
we ever took together.
I've just heard
so many awesome stories
about him.
Yeah. There's
a lot of those.
He designed some of the best
freefly formations ever.
He's a legend.
I take it he's the reason
you started skydiving?
Yeah.
He and his friends
made it look
so cool, you know?
Even when I was little,
I wanted to be just like him.
I'm sure he'd be
proud of you.
I wish my mom
thought that way.
After I made my first jump,
I think she was ready
to disown me.
I think that's
a typical reaction
from a mom, though, isn't it?
It was more than just that.
So I left.
Yeah, and now
you're back.
Yeah.
Great timing, huh?
[sighs]
I don't think
these last two days
have even hit me yet.
It's not going to be easy
when it does.
I just can't believe
what's happened.
[song continues]
[moaning]
[exhales]
That was...
unexpected.
- Are you complaining?
- Not at all.
So, what took you so long
to jump with us?
It's not
that I didn't want to.
It's just...
I've never been
good at making friends.
Why not?
If I don't let anyone
get close...
I can't leave
anyone behind.
Shouldn't you let the people
who want to get close to you
decide whether or not
they want to take
that chance?
Maybe.
But there's also
the flip side.
When somebody dies
at the drop zone,
it's easier
if it's... just some guy.
Harder when it's
your friend...
like Evan.
[sighs] Or Payson.
Listen,
what happened to Evan
was just bad luck.
And yeah, the timing is
a little weird, I admit.
But we're gonna find out
what happened to Payson.
And if he's dead?
Then at least he died
doing something
that he loved.
That's such
a fucking cop-out.
Don't you think
that Evan would be happy
to never make another skydive
if it meant that he
could still be alive?
♪♪
[plane engine whirring]
[male voice echoes] Hurry!
[clattering]
♪♪
[male voice, whispering]
Open the door.
[door bangs shut]
- [screams] Sarah!
- Greg!
[Greg screaming]
Greg, open the door!
♪♪
[screams] Oh, my God!
[screams]
Don't seem to have much luck
with the fellas, do you?
Two dead guys
and one missing
in so many days.
- And?
- And I'm just saying.
Doesn't exactly paint you
in the most flattering light.
[thunder rumbling]
[chair creaks]
Listen...
I don't think
that you did this.
But it did happen
under your roof.
Are you sure
there's nothing else
you want to tell me?
I've told you everything.
I'll be in touch.
[door clicks open]
- [groans]
- Lisa!
- You happy now?
- What the hell
is your problem?
You! You're
everyone's problem!
All of this started
when you came
to the drop zone!
You show up.
First Payson disappears,
Evan has a heart attack,
Greg goes home with you
and somehow manages to break
every bone in his body
in the middle of the night.
I don't know what your deal is,
but there is something
very wrong with you.
Come on, Lisa.
Just take it easy.
Take it easy?
Fuck easy!
How do you explain it,
Wade?
I don't know!
[thunder rumbling]
El Niño?
Stay the hell away from me.
Let's go, Wade.
Are you fucking serious?
She's not the bad guy
here, Lisa.
[scoffs] Keep telling
yourself that.
[door opens and closes]
You okay?
I need to get the hell
out of this house.
[thunderclap]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [faint music playing]
What's up, guys?
What are you
doing here? Two.
What else are you gonna do
when no one wants to jump?
Guess we're
in the right place, then.
Sarah, you okay?
Dude, Lisa went off on her.
Told her
that she was a jinx,
said that everything
that happened was her fault.
That's stupid.
I know, right?
That's what I told her.
- It's not you, Sarah.
- Mm-mm.
It's the Hex.
Oh, come on, Andy!
Not this horseshit again.
- Hey!
- No.
I can't name
one team, not one,
that's done it
and is still alive.
And I've been
here a while.
I mean, heck, Kris,
you've been here
longer than I have.
Can you?
Nope.
Okay, look, I'm-I'm
as superstitious
as anyone.
I touch the wing
of the plane before I get in,
I-I-I don't take
pictures before I jump,
but I don't believe
in any stupid Hex curse.
Come on!
[Andy] That's what Payson said
when I asked him not to do it.
He laughed at me.
He said, "Don't put
that bad juju
in people's heads."
He said you'd
mess up the jump.
So, I kept my mouth shut.
You could have said
something.
Would you have listened?
That's the problem
with you guys.
I mean, just the idea
of death makes things
more enticing.
Oh, come on, Andy!
It sounds like
total bullshit to me.
[chair drags]
Where--
where are you going?
To find out
if we're cursed or not.
Are you coming?
♪♪
When you said
that we were gonna find
some spiritual help,
I thought you meant
hire an exorcist or something.
Why? It's not like
we're being possessed.
Okay, that's a good point.
I'm not very flexible.
Just FYI.
Thanks, Dianne.
Sarah? [chuckles]
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Hi, Mom. This is
my friend, Wade.
- Hmm.
- You got a minute?
Um... of course.
You guys come on back.
What did the police say?
Nothing.
Guy's worthless.
I think I'm
their prime suspect,
if that tells you anything.
We need some help, Mom.
Well, I'm not sure
I can be much help, but...
let's start by centering
ourselves.
[Wade scoffs]
Find a comfortable
seated position,
something you can hold
for a while.
You can lie down,
if that's easier.
Ah! This is good.
Close your eyes
and try to relax,
- breathing easily
and deeply...
- [singing bowl ringing]
repeating the Sanskrit mantra
So Hum in your mind.
So on the inhale,
Hum  on the exhale.
So... hum.
♪♪
[laughing]
[Payson]
Yo, Andy!
Ingrid wants
to show you something!
[loud thud]
[plane rumbling]
What the fuck was that?
Everybody out!
Open the door!
[gasps]
What happened?
Did I pass out?
You didn't just pass out.
You had like a full-on seizure.
What did you see?
It was the day
we did the Hex.
The last time
we saw Payson.
Only it was different.
Something went wrong
with the plane.
Mom? What's wrong?
What is it?
It's, uh...
it's just been a long time
since I've heard that name.
What name?
The Hex.
Wait, why does your mom
know the Hex?
- How do you know the Hex?
- Mom?
After your father died,
people watched the video
of his death
over and over again
to see what went wrong.
But it was
just an accident.
It wasn't anyone's fault.
Sarah, if she's saying
that your dad died
doing the Hex,
I'm gonna flip my shit!
What I'm saying...
is it wasn't always
called the Hex.
Your father never
called it the Hex.
They only started
calling it that
after the other deaths.
The unexplained ones.
Unexplained deaths?
All but one
of your father's team.
And the other teams
stupid enough to try it.
They didn't all
necessarily die
on a skydive,
but it never ended well.
Eventually,
it just became...
the thing that people
talked about
around a bonfire.
Why didn't you ever
tell me any of this?
You had a hard enough time
dealing
with your father's death.
I thought I was
protecting you.
[beads rustling]
Take this.
Why? To meditate?
Just tell me what the hell
we're supposed to do now.
I wish I could.
[music playing on car radio]
So?
So what?
So, what do you think?
Are you sure that your mom's
not some New Age weirdo?
Talking about things
from like ten years ago?
That can't be
what's happening.
Do you really believe that?
Next time, we go
to the exorcist.
♪♪
Bet those solo skydives
look really good
right about now.
Nah.
[chuckles]
Jumping alone
all those years...
I was missing out.
I'm glad
we're in this together.
Fuckin' A.
Can't make it alone.
I wish Lisa
were here right now.
Why, so she could knock
some teeth out this time?
[laughs] No, I just feel--
I feel bad.
She's part of the team.
You know, whatever's
left of it.
I just feel like we should
stick together, you know?
♪♪
[light clatter]
[bottle clinks]
[laughing]
["King Vultures"
by Jay Ray playing]
[song stops]
I told you
not to come near me.
Look, we wanted
to warn you.
About what?
- You-you might need this.
- [beads rustling]
They-they are beads,
you know? Like beads.
I think the plane
was supposed to crash
the day we did the Hex.
Is that right?
And maybe
it was supposed to crash
because we did the Hex.
So, you're basing this
on a vision you had
while doing yoga?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
And you, Wade?
I was just
kinda lyin' there.
[scoffs] Okay.
Well, forgive me
if I don't take it
all that seriously.
Nothing strange
has happened to you, Lisa,
since Payson disappeared?
[gas hissing]
Shit! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Listen, I've heard enough.
So, thanks for checking in,
but I'm good.
You should go.
Lisa, come with us.
You shouldn't have
to do this by yourself.
None of us
should be alone.
All I am doing is looking
for a little peace and quiet.
Please.
[door closes]
["King Vultures" playing]
[music player stops]
[male voice echoing] Lisa...
[echoing continues]
Lisa... Now you... Lisa...
[coughs]
[gas hissing]
Lisa, Lisa, Lisa, Lisa...
Leave me alone!
[music restarts]
There's definitely something
she's not telling us.
[song continues]
So now what?
Wade.
[car alarm honking]
[fire crackling]
♪♪
[Wade]
How's our favorite Sheriff?
He says I'm a person
of interest
in an ongoing case,
and now I'm not supposed
to leave town.
What the fuck
are we gonna do, Wade?
Look, I knew that your turn
in there was gonna take
longer than mine,
and so I found myself
back at the bar.
Well, have you ever looked
at any of the old pictures
hanging on the wall in there?
Yeah, yeah,
I guess. Why?
Well, I don't know,
I never really paid
attention until today.
I found this hanging
on the wall in there.
- You stole a picture
off the wall?
- Look at it.
That's your dad's
old team, isn't it?
Does anybody
look familiar?
Yeah.
♪♪
What're you doing here?
What's-what--
what's that for?
Gophers and other pests.
Now, piss off.
I don't take visitors.
We want to ask you
about the Hex.
Why me?
Because we know
you did it, too.
All right, then.
Come on.
Sit.
I'm more of a beer guy.
Suit yourself.
You survived
the Hex. How?
[Wade] You knew
that we were gonna do it.
Why didn't you warn us,
or-or try to stop us?
Both good questions.
I ever tell you
about my first jump?
You've never said
more than two words
to any of us.
I was as good as dead...
the first time
I jumped out of an airplane.
All I had to do
to live again was pull.
That's intoxicating.
I went right back up again...
and it just wasn't
the same.
Get to your point.
To even come close
to that feeling again,
I had to push my limits
further and further.
Didn't help
that I wasn't born
with any natural talent
for anything.
Nah. My luck was going
to run out eventually.
I needed help.
Help? From who?
I prayed to God,
the Devil.
Out loud, hell,
even in my dreams.
In the end,
I think it was my soul
that conjured the demon.
[scoffs]
You, just like that,
you conjured a demon?
Not "just like that"!
Lanithro,
the demon of the air,
showed me
how we could use the Hex
to take what we wanted.
You want to know
how I survived the Hex?
I created it.
You... made the Hex?
Just imagine
what it feels like to know
that you've got
lives to spare.
I could... take any chance
I wanted, try anything...
consequences be damned.
I was given freedom...
freedom from death itself.
Because the lives of anyone
who tries the Hex...
then belong to you.
They're the sacrifice.
More.
I took more than their lives.
I-I took their abilities.
Lanithro took their souls.
It's a game he created
and never grew tired of.
- You lying son-of-a-bitch!
- [yells]
- Wade!
- [Kris groans]
What the fuck
did you really do?
Wade! Enough!
Get off of him!
[coughing]
[breathing deeply,
grunting]
[panting]
It was only ever supposed
to be one jump.
And then,
the rumors got started.
Human nature
was impossible to control.
People just had to see
for themselves.
I couldn't warn them,
and I couldn't warn you.
It became known as the Hex.
If that were true,
then you would be
immortal by now.
What are you still doing
in this busted-ass trailer?
That's not how it works.
I mean, do I look like someone
who's gonna live forever?
All those lives
are just second chances.
And I wasted all of them.
All I had left was my own.
Once that happened,
I quit skydiving altogether.
So, there's no way
to stop it?
How many deaths are you
responsible for?
♪♪
Are you responsible
for my father?
Sarah, get out of the way.
Wade, what are you doing?
Do you believe him?
[Wade] I don't know
what's happening,
but I know one thing.
I take him out,
and I end it.
- You don't know that!
- [panting]
What do you think, Kris?
Think this'll end it?
[sniffling]
Please, Wade. Don't.
No, no, no.
No, let him.
I want this.
I want this to end.
[breathing deeply]
Wait.
You never
answered my question.
Your father was
a good man, Sarah.
He didn't deserve
what happened to him.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
You motherfucker.
[screaming]
[sobbing]
[crying]
Sarah...
Sarah.
Open the door.
What?
[shouting]
Open the door!
[screaming]
[gasps]
[panting]
Sarah, where were you?
I don't know.
Uh... I was on the plane.
Before you did the Hex?
Yeah, I think so.
We were supposed to crash,
weren't we?
The plane wasn't
supposed to crash.
The plane is crashing.
Right now.
What?
This is how it happens.
This is how the Hex works.
You are not
where you think you are
or even when you think
you are.
You're occupying
the space and time
between when you know
you're going to die
and when you die.
And that space and time
can stretch out further
than you can imagine.
That's impossible.
You will continue to slip
between this waking nightmare
and reality
until you're dead.
You're running out of time,
but there is a way
if you'll let me help you.
That's impossible.
Do you have the altimeter?
Payson's altimeter,
do you have it?
♪♪
[engine revving]
Let's go!
Fuck, his seatbelt!
There's no time! Let's go!
Evan, you're next!
[loud honking]
[brakes screeching]
♪♪
Andy!
Thank God
you're still here.
Yeah, I'm here. I'm
just puttin' away the plane.
Holy Jesus, what happened?
Is that blood?
Whoa! Whoa!
[crying]
What's the matter with you?
Let's go, let's go!
Lost the right engine!
We're losing altitude fast!
We're super low!
Pull right away, guys!
Hey. Hey,
you're all right.
Just kinda faded
on me there
for a second.
You were right
about the Hex.
- We never should
have tried it.
- What?
Is that what this
is all about?
Andy, please.
I have to go now.
I have to jump.
It's the only way.
[panting]
I hope you know
what you're doin'.
♪♪
[shouting] Would you all
kindly get the fuck
out of my plane?
Lisa, now you!
Fuck! [screaming]
[gasps]
Sarah, run.
♪♪
[gasping, panting]
[Sarah] Oh, my God.
No!
Come on!
[grunting] Come on.
[crying]
♪♪
[sobbing in relief]
[grunting]
[crying]
[screaming]
You made it.
You have no idea.
You have no fucking idea!
What the fuck
is happening?
[panting]
You still don't know?
♪♪
So what's the Hex?
We've all
heard the stories.
A cursed skydive?
Are you kidding me?
That seems like a bad idea,
but what do I know?
But I don't believe
in any stupid Hex curse.
Come on.
[Kris] You are not
where you think you are.
You will continue to slip
between this waking
nightmare...
- [screams]
- ...and reality...
[loud thud]
...until you're dead.
[birds chirping]
What'd you tell her?
I told her
if she wanted to survive,
she had to jump
with your altimeter.
Gullible.
Just like her dad.
And this thing's
not a toy.
How else are you gonna know
how many lives
you're workin' with?
[laughs] That look on her face
was priceless, though.
You are one sadistic bastard,
do you know that?
You're definitely
goin' to hell.
And maybe
I can show you around.
Not anytime soon, Lanithro.
["137" by Jay Ray playing]
♪♪