Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[static scratching]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[ominous music]
[phone ringing]
[camera flashing]
- [Operator] 911,
what's your emergency?
- [Man] He won't answer.
He won't pick up
the phone for me.
It's Valentine's Day, I just-
- [Operator] Sir, try to calm
down. Tell me what's going on.
- [Man] I have to change.
I have to change.
- Sir, are you still there?
Are you okay?
- [Man] I have to change.
- [Man 2] What are you doing?
There's no time for this.
- [Man] Should I wear the black?
No, no, he loves green,
I'll wear the green.
I'll wear the green,
- [Man 2] We have
to get downstairs.
Stop this-
- [Man] No, I must change.
- [Man 2] Why, why
must you change?
- [Man] So that
he'll love me again.
We were a family.
I lost him.
- [Man 2] We have to get back.
You haven't lost him yet.
What are you smoking?
- [Man] It's not
crack, it's bass.
- [operator] Sir,
is everything okay?
- [Man] I just want to live.
- [Man 2] Hello?
- [Operator] This is 911.
Is there an emergency?
- [Man 2] Yes, we're
at the Lionsgate Estate
in Beverly Hills.
Please send someone.
- [Operator] Is anyone hurt?
[ominous music]
[woman screaming]
[upbeat music]
♪ With every little kiss,
there's a little heartache ♪
♪ With ever single thrill,
there's another heartbreak ♪
♪ The road is rough
♪ The road is tough
♪ Yes love is a hurricane
♪ Oh love is a hurricane
♪ When I'm in your arms
♪ My queen on the throne
♪ But when we're apart, I
walk the streets alone ♪
♪ One day happiness
♪ Next day loneliness
♪ Yes, love is a hurricane
♪ Love is a hurricane
[upbeat music]
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
- That was weird.
- Well that was something.
- Yeah, it was a lot like
the drag shows in Bangkok.
- You like Thailand?
- Oh, you don't?
Too bad we just missed
the performance.
- Too bad? Like you had
something better to do?
- I mean I figured
there were worse ways
to spend a solo Valentine's Day
than being paid to meet
some attractive ladies.
- Hmm, cheers to that.
[breathing heavily]
[ominous music]
[captive breathing heavily]
[mysterious music]
[breathing heavily]
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
[ominous piano music]
[singer mumbling]
It's okay.
[ominous piano music]
- Calvin, I take it you guys
got the 10K offer
as well, right?
- Eric, yeah, why
else would I respond
to this circus invitation?
Although I wouldn't be upset
if you two were
making more than us.
Two beautiful bodies
are worth a fortune.
Nice to meet you.
- Eva, I'm Eva.
- And I'm Cindy.
Word of advice, maybe next time
try not to objectify a woman
within the first five
minutes of knowing her.
[group laughs]
God.
What about you handsome, you
know how to treat a lady?
- My mother raised me right.
- You look kind of familiar.
Do I know you from somewhere?
- No, no, I don't think so.
I'm sure I would
recognize a girl like you.
- I'm Jason.
Glad to see you we're all a
normal looking group of people.
No obvious serial killers.
You never know with
these social experiments.
- What exactly does a serial
killer look like, Jason?
- Oh, I just meant, I was just
making a joke.
- He knows what you meant.
- I'm Jeff and I just got out
of a pretty bad relationship.
I figured a free dinner
and some entertainment
are good enough reasons
for me to leave the house.
Oh, and I'm vegan.
- Why does everyone who's vegan
have to tell you they're vegan
within the first five minutes
of meeting 'em, right?
- I was vegan
for two days, but I
like meat too much.
- I do too.
- Oh, well it looks like
Edward and Bella are sorted out
so if we could
just break through
the whole vegan culture here.
- Speaking of breakthrough,
did you guys read the invite?
What sorts of like
breakthroughs are we making,
like swapping childhood traumas?
- I was hoping for a
little more romance
and less head shrinking.
- Well, I do remember
a line on the invite.
I guess I figured it was
just matchmaker talk,
like which astrological
signs are the most compatible
and which have the best sex,
bullshit like that.
- That last line doesn't
sound like bullshit to me.
Pisces, right?
- Sure am.
- Yummy.
- Whatever it means,
I think this evening
calls for a group selfie.
Who's in?
- Here, I can take it.
- Hell yeah.
You'll send it to me or
maybe I should take it,
evidence in case
I get kidnapped.
- Nah, I got it, it's cool.
- You're doing it wrong.
Let me take it.
Okay.
Smile.
[camera flashing]
Cute.
- Huh, that's awesome.
It'll be a great story one day.
I do wonder though.
- What?
- What kind of person pays
a group of strangers $10,000
just to come to dinner?
- Perhaps a lonely one.
- Oh, Alfred's back.
- Though I care not to
speculate at my host's expense.
- I didn't mean any offense.
- None taken.
Ladies and gentlemen, follow me.
- Good job.
[mysterious music]
- Ooh, ooh, I see champagne.
- What can we do
for you, Alfred?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
your host has asked
that I obtained the signatures
on these waivers
here in front of you.
Just a simple formality,
I'm sure you understand.
And then Miss Cindy, I'll
fetch that champagne.
- Wait, waivers?
- Yeah, I'm not sure I follow.
- Basic contract
so we can get paid.
Sound about right, Alfred?
- Yeah, we shouldn't sign
anything without reading it.
- Dude, it's about the money.
- Master Eric is
of course correct,
although you're
more than welcome
to read the waiver
in front of you.
But it is simply to allow
remittance of your
compensation agreements
immediately upon completion.
- Of what?
- Of the evening, Master Jeff.
- What do we have to do?
- Simply be yourselves.
That's all your
gracious host requires.
- Shit, as long as
we get paid, right?
- You can say that again.
I am drowning in
grad school debt.
- Splendid.
And as per the master's wishes,
we will be indulging in a
technology free evening.
I'm sure you understand.
Your smartphones if you please.
- I'm not really sure-
- Old school rule, no
devices at the table,
my mother would be proud.
- Kind of refreshing.
I mean, who wants to try
to get to know someone
who's staring at
their phone, right?
Besides it's just dinner.
- Exactly and then we walk
out of here $10,000 richer.
- Yeah, I mean what's the
worst that can happen?
Besides my evening
feels lucky already.
- I mean, I don't
normally give up my phone.
I'm somewhat of
an influencer, so-
- Your parents must be
very proud, Miss Cindy.
- Thank you.
- Champagne.
- Are you following me?
- Am I following you?
- On Instagram?
- Oh, no, no, I don't
follow you on Instagram,
but I guess as soon as we
get our phones back I could.
- [Eric] Is an influencer
even a real job?
Like is how you pay your rent?
- Well, I do a little
bit of everything.
I do like, modeling and
acting.
- Okay, so why don't you
just tell people
you're a server?
- What do you do
for a living, Eric?
- I'm a motivational speaker.
- Wait, you're a
motivational speaker?
- Yeah, I could probably make
everyone's lives better here
in like five minutes.
You're all doing
something wrong.
- Like what?
- [Eric] Well for starters,
you responded to this
circus invitation.
- As did you.
- Are you gonna be an
ass the entire night
or just the first hour?
- Hm, you know I figured
everyone living around here
was in tech or acting.
- I'm getting my master's
in bioengineering
so that's not quite tech.
- So can you please tell us
why there's no surveillance
footage from last night?
Surely, a man as grand
as the one you're working
needs constant protection.
- It is a beautiful
home, isn't it, miss...
- My name isn't important,
but what's important is
you answer my questions.
Look just because
your boss is rich
doesn't mean he's above the law.
- Did you say your
name wasn't important?
- That's right.
- Well here I was thinking
nobody was above the law.
- What?
- It's my rudimentary
understanding of
this country's laws
that when being interrogated
by police officers
such as yourself,
you have a right
to ask for their name
and their badge number.
Is that not correct
or is it you that thinks you're
above the law?
- 2840.
That's her badge number.
- Its Agent Denver.
- Agent Denver, 2840.
- [Agent Denver] Mhm.
- How can I help?
- The CCTV recording
from last night?
- Yes, master's
very clear on this,
no recording of any kind
during social engagements.
- And why is that?
- Well, he's a
very powerful man.
Dines with the highest
members of society,
I'm sure you understand.
These men and women
value their privacy.
I'm sure you mean
anonymity, right?
- I couldn't say.
- Actually your
guests from last night
were not from high society.
As a matter of fact, they
were a bunch of 20 somethings
with pretty run off
the mill jobs, right?
- Yes, I mean nevertheless,
the social engagement
protocols are the same.
We switch off the
internal security cameras.
Who am I to question
my master's directive?
- Okay, so let me, let
me get this straight.
You never question your master,
even when four dead
bodies show up?
Did I state that correctly?
- Yes, it was a tragedy,
but how were we supposed to
know what would've happened?
- [Eric] What about you Eva?
- I work for the
state, social services.
- Ah, I can't imagine what
you see day in and day out.
- It's not always pretty,
but I get to be part
of the solution so
that some bad things be fixed.
- Well, if you're
looking for a broken boy,
you don't have to
look much further.
- [Cindy] Isn't that
like depressing?
- I think it's heroic.
I mean if you're not gonna
do something for money,
you might as well do something
that people respect, right?
But even I don't have
this kind of money.
- Should I be checking
these for like drugs?
- Don't worry, girl, I'll
watch your drink for you.
- Did you just call me girl?
Don't start sounding like a
motivational speaker over there.
- Lady, woman?
- Cindy works.
- Why don't we toast
to Valentine's Day and
social experiments?
- Um, the performer,
will they be joining us?
Where'd they go?
- Just to change, Miss Eva,
just to change.
Now if everybody would
like to accompany me,
please make your way
up to the dining room.
Our host is very eager for
the breakthroughs to begin.
I'll take your glasses.
Miss Eva.
Master Eric.
Master Jeff.
Master Jason.
Miss Cindy.
Mr. Calvin.
[ominous music]
- Well if nothing else,
the champagne's good.
- Yeah, it's decent.
- And the help's even better.
- I could certainly
get used to this.
- This is a beautiful house.
- Here's to this beautiful
house full of beautiful people.
- [Host] I'll drink to that.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
would you please stand?
Your host has arrived.
- Oh, no need for ceremony
with me, darlings, please sit.
- We thought you were
entertainment, no offense.
- No dear, that'd
be you, no offense.
Welcome.
Hello.
It's so nice to have you
gorgeous people with me tonight.
Eva, dear, you look stunning.
And look at that
figure, so nice.
It's a shame you cover
it up so much, mind.
Don't be bashful around me.
- Thank you.
- Don't be embarrassed.
- Cindy, look at you dear.
Look at you putting your
best stiletto forward.
May I borrow them sometime?
- I mean, considering how much
you're paying us to be here,
you can have them.
- Dear.
- I agree with Cindy,
that 10K was a
great fucking lure.
- Oh, what about love?
Eva, surely you must value
love over any amount of money?
- Oh, well it's like
a primal need, right?
Maslow and all.
- Yes, primal indeed.
And Jeff, didn't you
come here for love?
- Well, I figured I
can't do any worse here
than the local gay
bars and free drinks.
- Yes, free drinks, of course.
[ominous music]
Welcome.
Be a dear.
- Of course.
[ominous music]
- Each one of you has
been invited here tonight
for this special evening,
specifically, you were chosen,
and each one of
you will experience
your own personal
breakthrough tonight
within the next few hours.
There is love in the air.
You just have to be open to it.
- Thank you for having us, sir.
- Thanks, I'm really
enjoying this view.
- That's meat, right?
- Is this?
- Of course, it's vegan dear.
We wouldn't want to
upset your little system.
- No offense Jeff, but
I don't give a damn
about your vegan
lifestyle or whatever.
What I do care about
is making sure we get
what we were promised
here tonight.
- Yes, $10,000.
- Yes, Master Eric,
we must remind you
that you need to complete
your whole evening
in order to receive
your remittance.
- Damn, this is hot. Are
you trying to kill me?
- Please be careful, please,
I wouldn't want you to
get burned on my watch.
- Um, so the whole evening, how
many courses are we talking?
- It's not a question
of time, Miss Cindy.
You must complete your
personal breakthrough
and then you'll get
everything you deserve.
- Okay.
- Yes, Cindy, it's true.
You must stay and receive your
own personal breakthrough.
All of us, we must all stay
and receive our breakthroughs.
- Well, I pay $100 an hour
to a therapist once a week
and I haven't had
any breakthroughs,
but hey, if you're paying me.
- And we're here already, we
might as well enjoy ourselves.
- Yeah, we only live once.
- I might as well
have some carbs then.
Can I?
[dramatic music]
- Of course, dear, to
your heart's content.
[mysterious music]
- [Agent Denver] Are you
afraid of your employer?
Have you ever seen him
do anything worrisome?
- Good heavens.
No Agent Denver, I'm not afraid.
What a ridiculous question.
- She never questioned it,
but you're not afraid, right?
So what about the other guests,
anybody there you
were afraid of?
- Perhaps I've not been clear.
- How about this?
How about this?
Did your master use
illegal substances
when he entertained often?
- I'm not sure I know
what you're talking about.
- Hmm.
Friends in high places aren't
gonna be able to protect you.
- We'll see.
[dramatic music]
- We certainly
will see, won't we?
[ominous music]
- And last but not least,
a salad for Master Jeff.
- There seems to be
a pink and red theme
with the food tonight.
- You noticed.
It is Valentine's Day after all.
- Excuse me, I think mine
is a little undercooked.
- Oh dear.
- Speak for yourself.
Meat is supposed to be raw.
- I can assure you, Miss Cindy,
it's all sustainably sourced,
perfectly fresh and very safe.
Absolutely delicious.
- I wish I had my phone so I
could take a picture of it.
- Miss Eva, would you
prefer something else?
- Oh no, this is fine.
- Master Jason?
- Well I think if they
can handle it, I can too.
- Oh dear Jason,
you never know what you
might be able to handle.
Just like tonight,
you try it, you
might just like it.
[dramatic music]
- I mean, I'd try an
awful lot for $10,000.
- You're so sweet, dear,
I'm counting on it.
Thank you.
- I bet you'd try
a lot for 10 bucks.
- Hey, that's rude.
Apologize, now!
- Come on.
- Apologize!
[host giggling]
- Master Eric, we will
have a civilized dinner.
- I'm sorry.
The mind just gravitates
towards dark humor.
- Oh, it's okay.
The brain is a complicated
instrument after all.
- Is there a problem, Jason?
Can I help you with something?
- No, I just don't feel the need
to ask a host to make a
completely different meal
for my fleeting diet.
- Oh boys, so much
testosterone in the room.
Would you be a dear
and fetch my kitty?
- [Butler] Of course.
- Oh, I love cats.
- You're so cute.
- [Butler] Your kitty, sir.
[host sniffing]
- Angel wings.
Ketamine, anyone?
- I guess it's
that type of party.
- You're no fun.
The brain is a
complicated instrument,
but it can be predicted
and even manipulated.
- Manipulated?
- Oh, in only the best
kinds of way, dear Eva.
I bet your brain is
already telling you
that the person capable
of fulfilling those
deepest fantasies of yours
may be already in this room.
[dramatic music]
That person that could maybe
rescue you for a change,
even though you've
only just met.
- Come on, bro, she
deals with crazy all day.
- Are you saying you don't
believe in love at first sight?
- Are you saying you believe
in love at for sight, Calvin?
- I don't know, but I don't
want to count it out just yet.
- Oh dear, I think this
might just be lust speaking.
She is what the kids would
call a fine piece of ass.
- Hey.
- Oh, come on.
- I mean, I am.
- She is.
- I imagine it's rare,
love at first sight.
Maybe people sometimes
throw away all common sense
in pursuit of some
forever love but
it doesn't mean it's
impossible or crazy.
- You don't believe
love is crazy?
[Jeff clears throat]
- Sir, I mean, wait,
what do we call you?
- I don't think I'd mind
it if you called me sir.
- Okay sir, have you ever been
in love before or married?
[mysterious music]
- I was once.
They're not here anymore.
- The host isn't here to
answer your questions.
This evening is
about everybody else.
[mysterious music]
Sir, they're not here right now,
but we have six
wonderful guests.
- Okay.
Okay.
Six wonderful guests.
- Sir, perhaps they'd
like a demonstration, sir.
- To demonstrate what?
- Please.
[mysterious music]
- The insanity of
love of course.
Now which one of you is
brave enough to go first?
[mysterious music]
- Go first?
For what?
- Oh dear.
[ominous music]
- So these guests,
they were supposed to
perform party tricks for you,
is that it?
That's what you were
paying them for?
- Do not answer the question.
- I prefer not to
answer that question.
- So was it sexual
entertainment,
hmm?
I mean, we did find an
undergarment in the dining room.
- My client will not be
answering that question.
- Her client will not be
- And how did you pick
these six individuals?
I mean there must have
been something specific
about each one of them, right?
- My client will not be
answering that question.
- I prefer not to
answer that question.
- Are there any
God damn questions
that your client will
be answering today?
- Okay, hey, hey, how 'bout
we just do an easy one?
- An easy one.
- Why'd you invite 'em?
- Now this one's
worth answering, yes?
Have you ever been
in love, detective,
not lust, but true love,
the kind you'd give
your life's last breath
just to be next to them?
- Have you ever?
- See, lust is a
very powerful thing,
but it's fleeting.
My guests all needed
someone to love,
someone to belong
to in a real way.
So desperate were each of
them for a breakthrough
that they RSVP'd
for a circus show,
and my detectives,
what a show it was.
- You were the
ringleader, right?
- Ring leader, I think
that would be giving away
too much information, yeah?
So her client refuses
to answer that question.
- Lion tamer?
No daddy, perhaps maybe
I'm just the lion.
[ominous music]
- Sir, perhaps I
could prepare you
a little something from the
kitchen that you might like?
- No.
- Sir, you do need to eat
something in order to do-
- Fine.
Hmm?
Happy?
- Fuck it, I'll go first.
- I knew you would, dear.
Think of me as your
own personal cupid.
I can give you
anything you like.
You just have to
tell me what that is.
- To get laid and get paid.
It doesn't have to
be in that order.
- Damn straight.
- Of course, who wouldn't
expect such a response
from a red blooded
boy such as yourself?
[dramatic music]
[mysterious music]
Let the party begin.
Oh lovely.
Hi dear.
This is my friend.
The room as well as she
is free for you to do
with whatever you'd like.
- If I wanted to pay for sex,
I would've done it a
lot closer to home.
- Pay for sex, please,
you're my guest.
You're the one being
paid, remember?
She's completely free for you.
- I mean, I don't know
anything about this chick.
How do I know if she's, you know
clean?
- So many excuses after
all of the bravado earlier.
What, she not attractive
enough for you?
Do you need to see just a
teensie weensie bit more?
Love, please be a dear,
take off your clothes.
- This is turning into
some "Eyes Wide Shut" shit.
- This is getting
a little weird.
- Now could you
possibly find anything
to object about this body?
- This is messed up.
I'm not fucking a hooker
in front of a room
full of strangers.
- Oh sir, there's
a room upstairs
being made available for you
if you'll just follow me.
- No, see this is what
I'm talking about.
Predictable, your heart.
Here it is, it's
Valentine's Day, Eric,
you're single and
yet you won't bite.
- I don't need
this, bro, I'm out.
- Master Eric, you're
free to leave at any time,
but I must remind you
if you do leave before
your breakthrough,
you forfeit your compensation.
- Might be kind of hard
on a mechanic's salary.
- Mechanic?
- Oh, did I say too much, dear?
He was probably
trying to impress you.
Wait, perhaps we can come
to some kind of agreement,
a compromise of sorts.
- What kind of compromise?
What kind of compromise?
- Simple, you can
leave with your cash,
you just have to do one
little thing for me, please.
- And what's that?
- Strip, just down your boxers.
It's more than that
poor dear had on.
- I don't know
what that'll prove.
- Oh, come on.
And here I was thinking I
was doing you a favor, Eric.
Eric.
Don't worry, we won't
see any more than if
we were just frolicking
on a beach together.
It would be just like
wearing a bathing suit.
- No, I'm not stripping in
front of a room full of people.
- Why not?
- Because it's fucking weird.
- There's nothing
more I can do for you.
Show him the door.
[ominous music]
- Right here, huh?
What just there!
Is this what you wanted?
Take a good look, you sick fuck.
You obviously knew, right?
Is this why you chose me?
[host giggling]
- There's no need
to degrade him.
Hey.
It's okay.
It's okay to feel,
this isn't your fault.
- Do you see?
Do you?
Days of chatting,
hours wasted on Tinder,
weeks of meaningless dates,
and see these two, they would've
never found the connection
that I just gave to them.
- I'm sorry for being a
jerk tonight, I'm sorry.
- It's okay, I've been there.
- Maybe you would've found
this connection all on your own
after all.
Perhaps when you walked
in here, dear Eric,
you already knew Eva was going
to be your future, lovely.
- You really expect
us to believe
that your master is
some sort of matchmaker?
- No, you fool, he was trying
to teach the boy something.
- Teach him what?
It's what's inside that counts?
That age old beauty
and the beast bull.
Give me a break.
- He taught the boy confidence.
- Oh.
- And he did that by
stripping him down
both mentally and physically.
Once that boy removed his shirt,
he had no longer a need
to hide behind that
disgusting male bravado
he was demonstrating.
- So that charade was supposed
to teach him confidence?
Showing the whole room
his childhood scars?
Your master humiliated him.
- Confidence is the
ability to feel beautiful
without needing
to be told you are
and I'm done talking about it.
- What?
Do you think it's strange?
I just think it's
basic psychology.
- You and your basic psychology
can go fuck yourself.
- Oh, look at that breakthrough.
Make sure to give him
double the compensation.
- Double his compensation, sir?
- Did you not hear me?
Make it happen, please.
- It'll be done.
- Oh Eva,
don't be so upset, it's okay.
Please sit.
- Double just for
taking his shirt off?
I mean, I can top that.
- Darling, don't worry.
See, tomorrow Eric will wake up
a richer and more confident man
because you see,
he realized tonight
that there was just
nothing to fear.
There was just the little voice
right here inside of his head.
Please, don't be upset.
- You know what, guys like that,
really gets under their
skin when you make 'em wait.
They think their money
and their fancy lawyers
will let 'em get away
with murder, right?
Maybe it's time we taught him
that that's not
always the case, huh?
- So what are we gonna do?
- Wait.
- Alright.
- Master Eric, your car
will be here momentarily.
- Good.
- Sir, if I might be so bold,
your breakthrough just now,
it was, well it was inspiring.
Is everything all right, sir?
Oh, of course, I
beg your pardon.
Master Eric,
ah, your car, Master Eric.
- You think she's
worth all this?
- Master Eric, if something
is for you in life,
it will not pass you.
Godspeed, sir.
[gentle music]
[mysterious piano music]
- Ugh, I wish I had my phone.
I feel like, like
naked without it.
- Careful now,
you don't want to give
the host any ideas.
- Yeah, this is way
better than Tinder.
- Well, there's
certainly less weird ways
of meeting someone
and I'm not minding the
company so much tonight.
- Please eat.
Eat my lovelies.
[gentle piano music]
Bon appetit.
[dramatic music]
- My, what a show this will be.
- No, no, don't look
at me like that.
I'm not stripping down
and I don't have any
interesting scars.
Do Calvin next, he seems eager.
- Oh dear, I don't have
that kind of plan for you.
What our dear Eric needed
for his breakthrough
was completely unique to him,
as will yours be to you.
- Well, I'm not really a
breakthrough kind of guy.
- Oh.
I'm quite ordinary.
- Ordinary.
- Yeah, yeah, I know where
you're going with this,
but I mean you,
you haven't really given
as much of a choice.
I don't think this
is gonna work out so
I don't know
dramatically for us.
I mean you've only given me one,
you've only given
us one option and I,
I'm not really into black guys.
- Oh.
- What?
No offense, it's
just a preference.
We all have preferences.
- That's racist.
- No, no, it's not racist,
my sister is married
to a black guy.
- You know, having a
black family member
doesn't cure your racism, right?
- Yeah and it
certainly doesn't erase
hundreds of years
of conditioning
from slavery and
inequality and Jim Crow.
- Okay, so we're
all woke now, great.
[host giggling]
- The caucasity.
Would any of the white people
at the table care to know
what Jeff thinks perhaps?
- Yeah, it's racist as fuck.
- You can't call me racist just
because I have a preference,
a type.
- No, we can't call you racist
because it's not a
preference, it's a prejudice.
You've already made up your mind
about anyone with my skin color
and how they're unattractive.
A preference would be
not liking my hairstyle
or my taste in movies
or me getting to
know you this evening
and realizing you're
a fucking dick.
But you made your mind
up already at the outset
that you don't
like my skin color.
Of the two of us,
I'm better looking and
I have a better body
and judging by your
tired Zara suit,
I also have a
bigger bank account.
And judging by your
fucked up attitude,
I'm a better lay too.
And while you sit there
up on your high horse
with your pink pussy
and acting like your
shit don't stink,
know that it's me
who's too good for you.
So listen, snowflake,
I don't want you.
[group clapping]
[host giggling]
- Bravo.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to offend you-
- Your problem, Jason,
is that you overthink,
you overthink everything.
I know all about your
preferences, dear.
If you'd follow me.
[ominous music]
Master Jeff, right
up front there.
Master Jason, right
in the center,
this show is for you.
- Please.
These are your exes, yes?
They're certainly
not unattractive.
- So how did your master
end up with so much private
information about his guests?
- As I'm sure you're
aware, detective,
there is very little that
is sacred these days.
All this so-called
private information,
it's very publicly available.
All you have to do is spend
more than a cursory minute
on these young people's
social media platforms.
- Mm and did the guests know
that you were on their socials?
- I can assure you, detective,
that everything we
did was very legal.
Are you forgetting that
they signed waivers?
- Hmm.
- You know the problem
is they post so much
and on so many
different platforms,
it's really just a case
of piecing together
the information,
like one would with a puzzle.
- As you can see, I know
all about your tastes dear
and I think I also know
why none of these
relationships lasted.
You see Jason's always
looking down the road,
never happy in the here and now.
- How did you find them?
- Not to mention they
all look awfully pale.
- That's not fair, I've
definitely been with black men.
- Fucked black men, you mean?
And then you ran
your sweet little ass
back to your dorm room
to confide in your
cookie cutter gays
about how naughty
you were, didn't you?
Did you feel powerful?
Did they fawn over you
as you told them how
you did the one thing
their mommies and daddies
would never approve of?
- You're all ganging up on me.
- Dear, dear, dear.
I know this must
be so hard for you.
Aren't you just the teeniest
bit attracted to him?
You both like to travel,
I thought you'd have
so much in common.
Guess where his
favorite place to go is?
Thailand, just like you.
Jeff even has a little place
there on the beach, don't you?
You even drink the same brand
of whiskey for God's sake.
- Wait, how'd you know that?
- You should know Jason
that Jeff has never
cheated on a lover.
It means you can
trust him, dear.
I know trust is hard for you.
It's not surprising all
things considered, dear.
- I'll take you, for
example, detective.
Haven't you ever been
tempted to cyber stalk an ex,
find out what they're doing?
It's not hard and
everybody does it.
- How exactly did you find
out about the cheating?
'Cause we checked Jason's
socials, there's nothing.
- It was an interrogation
much like this one.
Oh, don't mistake my meaning,
they were free to leave at any
time, they weren't coerced.
I can give you the names of
Jason's ex-lovers right now.
They'll tell you
that they were more than
happy to talk to us.
Of course, they were
being handsomely rewarded
for their time.
I have a question,
is there anything illegal
about conducting a voluntary
45 minute polygraph,
especially if they've
signed consent forms?
- No, actually,
nothing at all wrong
with a voluntary test.
It just depends on what you do
with the information though,
doesn't it?
- Well the truth can never
be used as a weapon, surely.
- [Detective Denver] Hmm.
- Well, I guess we'll
find out, won't we?
- But of course,
this night was built as a
little less conversation,
a little more action.
[mysterious music]
So would you like
to know, Jason,
which one of these
cheated on you?
- What?
- You see, I know that
all of these relationships
ended with accusations
of cheating.
- Well, how could you
possibly know that?
- But you see, you were wrong,
at least two out
of the three times.
Isn't that sad?
Two out of three of
those relationships
might have worked out
if Jason didn't have
an issue with trust.
- That's not,
I don't know how you can know
anything about any of this.
You weren't there.
- No, I wasn't there,
but would you like to know
which one is the cheater?
- But how?
- Oh, a magician never
reveals his secrets,
but for you,
I offered each one
of your exes $5,000
to take a polygraph
test, a lie detector.
See, I rarely find people
that aren't willing
to spill their guts
about their exes,
especially to strangers.
So, would you like to know
which one of these
three is a cheater?
- It doesn't matter.
- It's all that matters, dear.
What if I offered to punish
one of the exes on your behalf?
Would it matter then?
- What?
- If you'd wish to know,
I'll double your take home,
right now, $20,000 just
like I did for Eric.
- But why?
Why are you doing this?
- This could be your
clean slate, Jason,
your tabula rasa.
And after you've done this,
you know that you
were wrong twice
and that the offending lover
will be punished on your behalf.
They'll never know
it's you though.
And then, I can work
on the rest of you.
[ominous music]
- So it turns out you might not
be as clever as you thought.
You confiscated everybody's
phone at the party, didn't you?
- Yes.
- Because you wanted everybody
to have a screen
free experience,
be in the moment?
- Yes, detective,
we wanted them to focus on
themselves and each other,
not their phones.
- [Detective] Right.
- Well, we have records
from all the phones at
the party that night.
And it turns out one of them
was still being used
after you collected them.
- I'm afraid that's not possible
unless it was Master Eric.
Master Eric left early.
- Nope, not Eric, uh huh.
Yeah, you took their phones,
but did it ever occur to you
that many people have other
devices that can send messages,
for example, a watch?
- Well, I didn't see any
smart watches on our guests.
- Well, it turns out
one of the new ones,
they look pretty much
like normal watches
and Jeff was a lover of gadgets.
[ominous music]
- Look, it's not worth it,
all right, trying to find out
what happened in the past.
Don't worry about that.
Who cares?
Don't be controlled
by money or revenge.
- Jeff,
I'm sorry, okay?
- For what?
- For earlier.
I mean no one's ever called
me out like that before and I,
I deserved it, every bit of it.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Look maybe, I don't know,
maybe I've been wrong
about the kind of
guys I'm attracted to.
Do you want to get,
do you want to get
a drink after this?
- I said I didn't
want you, all right?
- Seriously?
- I'm just, I don't
hate myself enough.
- Well, all this back and
forth is just exhausting,
isn't it?
Are you leaving or not, Jason?
- Yes.
- Sir, you're free
to leave at any time,
but of course, I must remind you
that if you do so before
your personal breakthrough,
you forfeit any compensation.
- I'd like to go.
- Are you sure, sir?
It's a lot of money.
[mysterious music]
- Which one?
- You knew we would
never work, Jason and I.
What's my breakthrough
or was I just collateral damage?
- Who was it?
- Master Jason,
I'm terribly sorry,
but from the moment
you asked to leave,
the host can no longer help
you or answer any questions.
You're done, sir.
[mysterious music]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
I've taken the liberty
of preparing a rather
delicious charcuterie board.
In the living room, if
you care to follow me.
And Miss Cindy, I
have more champagne.
Don't worry, Master Jeff,
all part of the show.
[mysterious music]
Please, enjoy.
Who'd care for some champagne?
- If you know, you
need to tell me.
- Master Jason, as
we've already stated,
the host cannot divulge
any further information.
However, he may not
be the only person
with something to share.
Master Jeff, Perhaps
you'd like some champagne.
- I'm sorry, I
truly had no idea.
- It was you.
- I suppose if
you'd like to know,
you'd have to take a seat.
[host humming]
- Do you know that Jeff
sent several messages
to his friends at dinner?
They were voice notes actually,
which means we could hear all
the voices in the background.
- And?
- I wonder if you
could explain this.
- This could be your
clean slate, Jason,
your tabula rasa.
And after you've done this,
you know that you
were wrong twice
and that the offending lover
will be punished on your behalf.
They'll never know
it's you though.
Is that it?
You can punish people
with the truth.
It's not a crime, is it?
- You want to explain
to your client
that inciting
violence is a crime?
- Me?
Can you prove I did
all the horrible things
you're suggesting, detective?
My knowledge of the law
may be a little rusty,
but if a threat was made
and then no one was harmed,
did an actual crime take place?
- Huh, exactly what threats
are we talking about here?
- Oh, none at all, my question
was merely hypothetical,
yes, hypothetical.
- I, I think I'd like to leave.
I can leave, right?
It's just, I don't know,
this feels like one
of those nightmares
where I can't wake up or like,
maybe I'm in the
middle of surgery
and I'm supposed to
be in a deep sleep,
but I can see the
surgeon and the scalpel
and I'm trying to
talk but I can't.
I just really don't feel good
about Eric leaving like that
and now Jason.
- Eva, my dear empath,
you're of course free to
go wherever you'd like,
but I assure you Eric is fine.
Would you like us
to give him a call?
I can give him a call
right now if you'd like
and then you'd see that
he's perfectly safe
and also $20,000 richer.
And then you can be free
to continue your
journey with us tonight.
Eric?
- [Eric] Hello?
- Hi dear.
We were just wonder,
well actually,
Eva was just wondering
if you were okay.
She thought our driver
might have left you
for dead somewhere.
- Oh, I didn't say that.
- I assured her you
were perfectly fine.
- [Eric] I'm good.
In fact, I just got to my
favorite neighborhood dive bar.
You ever been to Hank's?
If Eva ever wants to
find me, I'm there a lot,
maybe too much.
- Yes, dear, I'm sure they have
perfectly lovely cocktails.
Listen, for the rest
of us, we're curious,
did you check your bank account?
- [Eric] Oh yeah
and I was damn happy to
see a $20,000 payment.
Hey, is there any way I can
talk to Eva for a second?
I just-
[phone beeping]
- See, perfectly fine.
- He said Hank's, right?
- I think so.
Sounds dirty.
- Sounds perfect right now.
Don't worry, I think
that's my cue to go.
I really do think
I should leave.
- It has been a
bit intense tonight
and I think I should go too,
but thank you for
a lovely dinner.
- If she's leaving,
my intended date,
then there's not much
left for me to do here.
- Eva, darling,
I understand love is
finally waiting for you.
Your car will be
called immediately.
Who would I be to stand
in the way of that?
And Jason, you've made
it perfectly clear
that you don't want us
analyzing all your
past relationships
so if you'd like to
go, please leave.
Calvin, Cindy, I wonder if
you'd stay with me for a while
if I offered you
Jason's compensation,
$10,000 a split
between the two of you.
- Oh,
is there dessert at least?
- She can have mine, I
don't do sugar really,
but I'm game, this is fun.
- Jason, I did not know
it was you, I swear.
- No, but you knew about me.
You knew there
was some poor fuck
who's lover was walking
out on him for you.
Isn't that just as bad?
[ominous music]
Who was it?
Richard, Steve or Allen?
- [Jeff] I will not dignify
that with an answer.
- So tell me about Eva.
- I already told you.
- No, you said
she asked to leave
right before Jason
lost his mind.
- So I escorted her out.
- And that's it?
- What else would there be?
Ah, Miss Eva, I paged your
car, it'll be here momentarily.
I am so sorry about
things getting a
little heated upstairs.
These things do happen,
but fear not, the car's on
the way, no need to run.
There.
- I'm just worried about Jason.
I feel like maybe he
should leave and cool off.
- Miss Eva, some men's
tempers can't be quelled,
best not to get involved.
Miss Eva, was there
something else?
- I was wondering,
is there any way I could
have Eric's number?
- Miss Eva, I'd be delighted to,
but as per your waiver
agreement, I'm sure you know,
you're not allowed
to communicate
with anybody in the
breakthrough experiment
unless you made a
joint breakthrough,
which I'm sure Master Eric
would've intended but alas.
- So there's no way?
- I really wish I could.
But perhaps, Miss Eva, the
universe will hear your prayers.
Your car should be
here momentarily.
Would you excuse me?
[gentle music]
- Jeff stopped sending voice
notes at 9:53, why is that?
- I do feel quite badly
about what happened then.
That's about the time
things got just out of hand.
- Out of hand?
Four people were killed.
- And you know, technically
that is mass murder.
- How was I to know
what would happen next?
- Four fucking people.
- Yes, four fucking people.
You will not dignify
that with an answer?
You gonna let him
get away with that?
Wouldn't you like to know
which one of your exes
didn't think you were any
better than some black guy?
- I'm not playing this
sick game, you hear me?
- Who was it?
- Do something.
- So for the record,
who attacked who first?
- I beg your pardon?
- Which guest at your
dinner party from hell
killed which other guest first?
- You know, it all
happened so fast,
I don't know if I
could definitively say.
- Right, and you said that
Jeff acted in self-defense,
are you sure?
- Yes.
- So if we asked your
master, would he be able to--
- He wasn't there.
After I came back from
escorting Miss Eva out,
he'd stepped out for a moment.
- Stepped out?
- Just for a moment, yes.
[ominous music]
- Who was it?
- Why does it matter now?
- Guys, stop.
- I'll stop when he
tells me who it is.
[mumbling in other room]
I'm gonna count to three
and you're gonna
tell me who it was.
Okay?
Was it Richard, Steve, or Allen?
One.
- Party's over guys, seriously.
- Two.
- Please, just stop it, okay?
- Three.
Who was it?
- Guys!
- Who was it?
[mysterious music]
Tell me who-
- Relax, relax!
- Tell me the name!
Tell me who it was!
[glass shattering]
- [Cindy] Call 911.
[ominous music]
- Oh shit.
- Your butler says you
stepped out of the room
when Jason and Jeff
began fighting.
- Mmhmm.
- In the middle of
a heated argument?
- Yep.
- Where'd you go?
- To change, dear.
- Are you serious?
[ominous music]
[Jason groaning]
- Call 911.
Do something!
There's too much
blood, I can't stop it.
Do something, please.
What the fuck are you two doing?
Seriously, call somebody.
He's dying, help him.
Jesus christ.
There's too much
blood, I can't stop it.
- Oh, you're never gonna
get all that blood to clot.
Jason's a hemophiliac.
- I can't take the rap for this.
Am I gonna take
the rap for this?
- The rap? Oh, we're
all your witnesses.
Right, we all saw Jeff
cut Jason's throat?
- [Cindy] Oh my God.
Oh my God.
- You could have stopped this.
You made this happen.
You did this.
Fuck!
- Jeff, calm down, please.
- You calm down.
- Jeff, you're making it worse.
Please calm down.
- Just shut up, just
shut up, let me think.
- Jeff, stop.
- [Jeff] Oh my God.
[dramatic music]
- Calvin.
Calvin, no.
Calvin, stop, please look at me.
- How's it going?
- Calvin, no, no, no, no, stop.
[dramatic music]
- It's okay.
- You killed him.
- Well at least they didn't
kill the black guy first, huh?
- [Detective Denver]
You didn't stop them?
- How could I have?
I had no weapons.
Obviously no superior strength.
- So even as things
progressed, you did nothing?
- I certainly had no idea what
was about to happen, okay?
And when it did, uh.
- Yes?
- How were we to know we
invited a sociopath to dinner?
Not my fault, mere coincidence.
- What are you doing?
Why would you kill him?
Calvin!
- There you are, Calvin.
- Oh my God.
- I was hoping you'd come
out to play with us tonight.
It's okay, you're
safe here with us.
- Did you guys call 911?
- Of course I did.
- No, you didn't.
- There's nothing you
can do more now, dear,
than just breathe.
[breathing heavily]
- What are you guys doing?
You killed him.
You fucking killed him.
Calvin, why would you kill him?
Who the fuck are you?
Who are you?
- Who the fuck are you?
See, I don't like being played.
- Oh dear, we didn't mean
to make you feel used,
certainly not our intention.
Should we let Cindy
in on the secret?
[ominous music]
- So help me out with
something, will you?
- I'm being as open
and transparent as
I can at all times.
- Good.
Well, imagine you
were me, all right?
And as me, the person
sitting in front of you,
well you know they're
guilty, but something,
boy, something's just not right.
- My client will not play.
- Oh it's okay, I don't
mind a little role play.
- Well, thank you.
- Oh, consider your
fantasies indulged, daddy.
- I appreciate that.
So something, something's
just not right,
or more to the point,
maybe it's just that
something's not quite adding up.
- What would that be?
Please tell.
- Why?
A motive for him
doing what he's doing?
- Maybe there isn't one.
- Well, 30 years on the
force would tell me,
if you don't have a motive,
then you don't know
the whole story.
- Like a puzzle?
- Exactly.
- You think you're missing
a piece, don't you?
- That's because I am.
I'm missing a piece.
[hand slamming on table]
[host giggling]
- How dramatic of
you, I love it.
- What's that?
- Well, I'm no technical expert,
but looks to me
like a shitty TV.
- No, see, you have 12
state of the art TVs
in and around the house
but that is a very,
very special monitor
designed solely to
receive a live feed.
- Is that so?
- That is so, tech
guys just confirmed it.
- Well take another look.
Yeah, it still looks
like a shitty TV to me.
- You know what it
looks like to me.
- What?
- A motive.
A motive.
- A motive?
- Did you know, dear,
that there are only an
estimated 20 serial killers
in the US at any given time?
Our Calvin has a tendency to
fill into his basest of needs
every single Valentine's Day.
So have you shown up?
- What?
Why did you lie to me?
- Such a bad boy, Calvin.
- Stop it, you're scaring her.
- You lied to me.
- I'm scaring her?
That's not even the best part.
You know, Calvin here's been
watching you for months and,
I'm sorry to be the
bearer of bad news but
the boy isn't even a Pisces.
- Who are you?
You lied to me.
[ominous music]
Oh my God.
- Hey, hey, hey.
I'd never hurt you, huh?
In fact, I just want to love you
like the princess you are.
Jeff was, well
Jeff killed Jason.
What was I supposed to, huh?
What if he turned on you?
Hey, it's gonna be okay,
I promise, I promise.
I just want to love you.
I can be whoever you
want me to be, okay?
I can be like Frederick then
with the heart of a mason.
I can work out like that
guy you liked, Michael,
and I'll get you a
coffee every morning
from your favorite coffee house.
Arbeus, right?
White chocolate mocha.
- Fuck you, get away from me!
[ominous music]
Get away from me, all of you.
- Hey, we're gonna
be fine, okay?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Stay away, I'm serious,
get away from me.
- What are you gonna do, Calvin?
You killed this poor boy
on Valentine's Day
for Christ's sake
in front of all these
witnesses with your history.
- Stop it.
I need to think.
- What happened?
What'd you do?
- Stop.
- [Eva] What'd you do?
- Eva, stop, let go.
- Shit.
[host and butler giggling]
- What have you done?
- I didn't mean to.
I'm so sorry, I
wouldn't hurt anybody.
- You know what I
just can't figure out?
- I should think
you can't figure out
a great deal of things,
detective.
- The why.
Like why did he do it?
- Sociopaths must be
so hard to predict.
- No see, that's
just it, they're not.
They're not hard
to predict at all.
You just gotta know how
to stimulate 'em, right?
Like a dog wanting a bone.
- It's not my area, I'm afraid.
- My question to you is,
are you that dog?
Are you that dog
just waiting to respond
to his master's command?
Is that you?
- Detective,
you really are clutching
at straws now, aren't you?
- 'Cause I'll tell
you what I think.
I think the two of you
invited a sociopath to dinner
and you just made
an educated decision
to trigger him exactly
when you needed to.
Is that what happened?
- Could you tell me why
we would want to do
something like that?
- See that's what
I can't figure out.
- You can't,
not with all that wonderful
imagination you have?
- I can't.
- Tell me, detective,
is it a requirement
of the police force
for you to be so creative?
- It is.
- Calvin, Calvin, Calvin!
Witnesses.
[ominous music]
- Calvin!
[Eva breathing heavily]
Someone help!
[ominous music]
[Eva breathing heavily]
[doors shaking]
[dramatic music]
[Eva screaming]
- Eva.
What made you do that?
[ominous music]
[Eva crying]
[gunfire blasting]
[gentle music]
[Eva crying]
- Hey, hey Eva, hey, you okay?
Are you okay?
[Eva crying]
[gentle music]
- [Eva] You came back?
- For you.
For you.
[Eva crying]
[gentle music]
- [Detective Denver] Thank
you for taking the time
to talk to me again together.
I know this whole thing was
quite the ordeal for you.
- Of course, we
just want to help.
- So you came back
to the mansion?
But why?
After the host humiliated
you, you came back.
- There was something not
right about those two.
And when they hung up on me,
well I just had a feeling in
my gut that Eva was in trouble.
You ever have that,
that gut feeling?
- Yeah, it's called instinct.
I'd probably be dead
without it in my job
and it's a damn good thing
that you listened to yours,
but you brought a gun.
So why not call the police
if you're worried
enough to bring a gun?
- And say what?
I was at a dinner party earlier
where they humiliated
me for $20,000
but now all of a sudden,
I think they're murderers?
It wouldn't have made any sense.
It still doesn't make any sense.
I do have a permit
though for the gun.
- Thanks for cooperating.
We may need this later.
For now you can have it back.
Don't lose it.
- I mean I just, I had
to get back to Eva.
I just thought, you know, to
bring the gun just in case.
All right, that place
was sketchy as hell.
When I got there, heard
screams, her screams.
- I...
- So I ran to them.
My heart just kind of took over.
I didn't want to hurt
Calvin or anything,
all right I really didn't,
but there wasn't another option.
- I understand.
I don't think you have
anything to worry about,
seems like pretty cut
and dry self-defense.
Eva, I know this is difficult,
but do you remember
anything else?
Anything that could help us
piece together who these men
are and what they wanted?
- I've racked my brain trying
to think of anything else but,
I was gone for probably 15
minutes waiting for that car.
When I got back,
the host, it was like
a different person.
I can verify what Eric
was saying though,
at least about,
about the stuff when
I was in the room.
You know what?
I didn't mean to-
- Honey, that's enough.
- It's okay, the brain
takes over in these moments,
it's fight or flight
and your fight instinct
told you to get that knife.
- Look, she needs her rest.
- Sure.
It might have saved your life.
You did good.
Don't worry.
We're gonna untangle this mess.
Don't let him leave.
- Thank God that's over.
- Hey,
how did you know
I was in the room?
- What do you mean?
- I wasn't screaming.
- Well, I heard something.
You're just tired.
You need to get some rest, okay?
Just let me take care of you.
- So I got four dead kids
and two traumatized for life.
Then there's you
and your butler.
And you know you don't have
to actually pull the trigger
to be a murderer,
right, you know that?
- Surely the serial killer
wanted in one, two, three states
is your first suspect.
I don't want to tell you how
to do your jobs detectives,
but for me it's
just an obvious now.
- I'm sorry, what
did you just say?
- Calvin, I heard the
lady cop over there
say that Calvin was
a serial killer.
- No, you just said he was
wanted in three states.
- Calvin told us.
When things got violent,
he told us he was
wanted in three states.
- See but you
didn't mention that.
You said he attacked Jeff to
protect Cindy, is that right?
- Yes, that's what I said.
There was also a lot
of other shit going on.
It just must have
slipped my mind.
- Right.
- Let's talk about Calvin.
He was wanted, right,
in three states?
- I'm not sure I would
know that information.
- I don't think I need to
tell you this at this point,
but your buddy has
thrown you to the wolves,
but you can still save yourself,
we can make a deal.
Why don't you just tell us
everything that happened
and we'll call the DA?
- Detective, all we did
was host a Valentine's
Day dinner party
and we told our
young impressionable
guests some truths.
But you know what
the real truth is?
Love hurts.
- Copy that.
Sorry, detective, but
we just got a call.
- [Detective Denver] From who?
- The DA.
- How is Charlie?
- But he hasn't made a deal yet.
- Not for a deal.
Turns out we are to suspend
interviews immediately.
[mysterious music]
- Friends in high places.
- I wanted to say thank you.
- For what?
- For coming back, saving me.
[gentle music]
- I'll always be here for you.
You need to get some rest.
- Will you be here
when I wake up?
- I will.
I always will.
- Look I wish I had more
but that's all I got.
The DA said we gotta let him go.
- Well what kind of
bureaucratic bullshit.
- That guy's just seized
Calvin Thompson's laptop.
Thousands of pictures
of Cindy Bellshaw,
the gym, coffee shop,
this guy had been
stalking her for months.
- He knew, he knew
he'd been caught
'cause I asked him about Calvin
being wanted in three states.
- He was wanted in five states.
- I know.
- Well I'll tell you,
they've been researching Calvin
probably for months
prior to the dinner.
I'll tell you another thing,
if Calvin's ever admitted
how many states he was wanted
in, he would've said five.
- They fucked up.
They fucked up and now the DA
says we have to let them go.
What kind of justice is that?
- Detective, you know
you have no right
speaking to our client.
- Oh, it's quite all right.
You know we're innocent
now, don't they?
- No, we know you did it.
We know you're responsible
for those kids' deaths
and that you pulled
the strings somehow
and we're gonna prove it.
We'll get a break,
you just wait.
- Master, I do wonder,
perhaps we should
invite the detectives
over for dinner sometime.
- Perhaps.
- Detectives.
- [Man] Eva.
Eva!
Murderer!
- [Nurse] Dr.
Remington, dial 2226.
- Can I help you guys?
- No.
- Oh, we're here just visiting
an old friend, thank you.
[mysterious music]
- I hope everything
was as ordered, sir.
- You've done well.
You're really not
a half a bad actor.
I'm lucky to have such
great talent at my disposal.
Oh yeah, of course.
They're still there.
But I'd get there sooner rather
than later if I were you.
- My family had nothing
to do with this,
you fucking monster.
- I just needed the insurance
to make sure you were
on top of your game.
- Was everything
as expected, sir?
- Oh yeah, played out perfectly.
- Wonderful.
- And he was right,
she was just a girl
who needed to be saved.
The things we do for love.
- Indeed, sir.
Be a good boy.
[mysterious music]
- For Eva.
- Aw, I almost forgot.
Happy belated Valentine's Day.
You can go now.
- Enjoy the rest of
your evening, sir.
- I think I will.
[ominous music]
[gentle piano music]