(explosion)
(high pitch sound)
(scrubbing)
You can't see germs, but they can see you,
mingling and scurrying
about without consequence
while they silently destroy our world.
(scrubbing)
The only way to stop them from spreading
is to kill every last one of them.
Tonight, a new travel warning, now
requiring all airline
passengers to test negative
before they can enter the U.S..
In the last 24 hours, 3866
Americans have died due to the virus.
Many in the new American
epicenter of California.
I'd say even
as we go into a Level 4,
we will continue to see a rise in cases
for at least 15 days
so that numbers will continue to increase
before they turn around.
Hospital staffs are working around
the clock to keep these people from dying.
(coughing)
This morning, a highly contagious strain
detected overseas for the first time
in England has now made its way
to the United States for the first time.
It was found in a man
in his twenties who had not traveled.
(coughing)
We are now seeing so
many people who
are congregating indoors
where we know the virus concentrated.
A lot of Americans
demonstrating the worst type of behavior
unmasked in close quarters.
So this is invariably gonna be
a superspreader event.
More than 22,000 people in the state
now hospitalized with the virus.
Paramedics describe scenes inside
emergency rooms like a war zone.
Morgues and funeral homes are running
out of space to put the bodies.
L.A. County bringing in refrigerated
trucks to store them.
(camera flashing and whirring)
An increase in daily cases more than 88,000,
America has also just set a one week
record for new cases.
Today, the L.A. County
health director said that
ten people become infected every minute.
But if you remember, at the beginning
of the pandemic, California
was one of the first
to shut down and flatten the curve.
Where did things go wrong?
Insects ruled the
skies long before any other creatures.
- If you're wondering
where things went wrong,
then you haven't been paying attention.
Look around. Things have been going
wrong for a while.
- Relentlessly adapting in shape and function.
Nothing could stop.
♪ There’s a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you.
♪ There’s a call on the phone for you.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call
there’s a call for you.
♪ There’s a call on the phone for you.
Wakey, wakey, lackey. lackey!
- I'm up, I’m up.
- Are you sure? Because you look dead.
- I'm fine. I just had some green tea.
- You gotta on top of your game, okay?
You hear the morning news?
Your work wife, Rodriguez, she’s
not coming in today.
- Shit! Shit!!
- She called me late last night.
Little weeny kid got sick again.
- Well, when’s Patel coming back?
- That son of a bitch.
He's still stuck in Texas. He's
too afraid to fly in a plane.
I got nothing but a bunch of pussies
working for me.
Help me, ‘Rick.
- So...
so, it's just me?
- This is your chance to shine.
I wanna see you up on that wall
for once.
-  I'm...
It's just, I get swamped with the
the front desk and room calls,
I don't think the
housekeeping is something...
- Take a deep breath.
(long breathing)
Okay? It’s just for a short time
until everything gets better.
- I don't know how to...
I can't do the housekeeping
with the linens and the germs
and cleaning the toilets and...
and the front desk.
- Okay, okay.
I'll pay you time-and-a-half. Okay?
- Well, that helps...
It's not something I'm comfortable doing.
- You wanna shut down?
- I can’t...
- Corporate’s not gonna like it
if we go bankrupt.
No motel, no job. Do the math.
- I think there's someone
in the motel with the virus.
I hear coughing through the walls.
- What? You've been keeping an eye
on them through the cameras, haven't you?
- Yeah.
- Okay, then there's no one, Tarik.
- I swear someone’s definitely sick.
- There’s no one here that has the virus.
I would know.
Trust me!
Just use the PPE, gloves,
masks, sprays, the outerwear.
You'll be fine.
Oh, Tarik, the most important --
Six feet, okay? Six feet!!
When faced with stress,
you have to remain calm.
You have to take care of yourself.
People are relying on you.
This is what it means to be essential.
And now it's just me. Flying solo.
- Almost 100,000 small businesses have
permanently closed due to the pandemic.
And unlike the Spring, there is no help
in sight from taxpayers through Congress.
You are your own best defense.
These people aren't
going to stop the virus.
Some of these people are the virus.
They don't sanitize.
They don't wear masks.
They don't social distance.
Just a bunch of selfish fucks.
(coughing)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call on
(beep)
- Dad?
- Tarik!
- How you doing?
- I'm doing about the same. How’s
everything there, my son?
- Oh, you know, same day, everyday.
- The home care place called.
They said they didn't get the payment.
- What? No, I gave them the credit card
information yesterday.
- I don't know what's happening.
- I'll take care of it.
You have all the medicine, right?
- I do, but...
- But what?
(clears throat)
- You should not worry about me, my son.
You need to look after your health.
Have you been checking with Dr. Avery?
(coughing)
- I just care about you getting better.
I'll make sure everything is taken
care of, and I'll visit as soon as I can.
Okay, Dad?
- Okay!
But you need to make sure you keep up
with the news there.
(coughing)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you,
♪ there’s a call on the phone
for you.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you...
(beep)
Super Six front desk.
How can I help you?
(tv noises)
- You called?
- Yea, good. You're here
to defuse the bomb.
- No, I'm from the front desk.
- Yeah, come in.
(tv noises)
- Could you ...?
- Oh, yeah. Sorry.
- Thank you.
She seems nice, but she's not your friend.
She's just another lunatic pretending
like nothing is going on.
- Uh, sorry.
My boyfriend is a caveman.
- Don’t worry about it. Seen a
million of these.
You got here yesterday,right?
- Yeah, we did.
- Yeah, I remember,
with the musician.
- Yeah.
- Is that your boyfriend?
- Uh huh.
- He any good?
Oh, I... I meant musically. Sorry!
- Oh, yeah. Yes, yes, yes.
He's good. He's really good.
He's actually a rapper.
(tv noises)
Yea, a producer heard him on SoundCloud
and invited him out to L.A.
Cool. A SoundCloud rapper.
Like the world doesn't have enough of those.
- Waddup, baby?
- Hey, hey...there’s a guy
- Oh, what’s up?
(plunger noises)
(tv noises)
- Thanks for unjamming my
log, bro.
- Chad!!
- What?
(tv noises)
- That Mexican place fucked
my stomach.
- You don't have to tell the guy that.
(flushing)
(tv noises)
- Hey, thank you doggie!
(water pattering)
- The Head of the Hotel
Association of New York City says
it is the worst crisis they’ve experienced.
One of the hardest hit states
during the pandemic...
- On the verge of the most promising contact,
there is too often unexpected frustration.
(phone chimes)
More than half of the time,
the outer is soaky and shrouded in rain or mist.
(tv noises)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call on
♪ on the phone for ...
(beep)
Tarik, did you clean the three rooms
I asked you about?
- Yeah, of course I did.
- You missed room 222, dumbass.
I just checked.
Wait, I thought you were at the other location.
You're at the motel?
- Where else would I go?
I had to come quarantine myself.
Okay, but are you sure about the room?
I thought I did it right around 10 a.m..
It's 9:45, Tarik.
Come on, Tarik. You
gotta stay on top of things.
You gotta take charge here.
I can't keep checking on every little
detail. It’s the slowest time in history.
We don't have that many guests.
You're doing a sloppy job like this.
Come on. You're better than that.
- I'll take care of it right now.
(beep)
I don't get paid enough to clean up
after these people.
Sometimes I wonder if they were raised
like this or if this was just gradual.
Shit! What the fuck?
Just clean it up!
Fuck, God it’s staining the mattress.
(coughing)
Breathe. Fuck! Fuck!!
There’s so much.
- You missed room 222, dumbass.
I just checked.
(coughing)
Shit!! Shit !!! Shit!!!
No one’s gonna find out.
Fuck, it won’t go away.
Everything is going to be fine
if you remain calm.
Just breathe.
You have to breathe.
(panting)
Breathe! Breathe!! Breathe!!!
(voice message beep)
Hi, Tarik, it's Melanie from
Dr. Avery’s office again.
Just trying to get a hold of you to see
when you'd like to reschedule
your sessions from last month.
Give me a call back when you can, so that we can
squeeze you in sooner rather than later.
(phone hangs up)
- Waddup dawg!!!
- What the fuck are you doing?
My bad, man, I didn’t mean to scare you.
Hey, I was going to ask you,
do you have any AA batteries for the remote?
- No, I don't know. I'll
bring them over if I have any.
- Alright, man. Appreciate you dawg,
I'll just be waiting by the room.
(coughing)
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
If he has it, she could have it.
Anyone in the motel could have it.
They both violated the six feet,
so that doubles my chances
and then doubles again for everyone
I come into contact with. Shit!!!
Fuck!!
(panting)
You selfish circus freak.
Justin Bieber. Fuck you!!
- Yes, that is not what I was talking about, man.
(mouse clicking)
That verse with that hook.
(coughing)
The fucking bastard gave me the virus.
That was the one I agree with you works.
That verse with that hook.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Jay help me write that one. It’s fire, right?
I know. Oh, let me. Oh, shoot.
Let me call you right back, bro.
Yes, I'll call you back. Alright, peace.
What’s up man? Did you ever find
those batteries, bro?
- No!! You gotta leave, pal!!
- What do you mean?
Dude can't smoke a cigarette
without getting kicked out of the motel?
- No, it's the coughing and sneezing.
- I’m sorry? What? Were you spying on me?
Fucking FBI looking at you.
- Hey don’t
don't touch that.
It's for the safety of the motel.
I just saw you coughing
out in the hallway.
You're not even wearing a mask.
-  Are you fucking insane bro?
- Hey, hey, hey..
What's going on?
- What is up with this dude, Katy?
- It's for the safety of the guests.
- I told you I got nothing.
Are you deaf? Shit, man.
I’m gonna give you some rave reviews, alright?
- Alright. Okay.
He was trying to kick us
both out of the motel
‘cause I coughed.
- Chad, that’s enough.
- No, he's sick.
- No, he is not sick. He has allergies.
- It's probably ‘cause you got
some skunky-ass dead
animal laying around this lousy motel.
- Yeah, well, that sounded
more like the dying type of cough.
- Dying kind. Hey man,
get out of here, alright?
You are stupid.
- Ok, alright.
Look, he, he doesn't have anything.
Alright? I would know. He's fine. Okay?
Can you trust me?
- We have clear scientific evidence that
they work and they are our best defense.
- The head of the CDC there once again
imploring people to wear a mask.
(coughing)
- As blood flows, bitter rivalry has aroused.
As always, the kill is watched
from the shadows.
The hyenas identify the lions.
(knock on window)
(buzzing)
- Hey. I'm sorry about
what happened back there.
He's sort of got a short fuse.
- What's up?
- Do you have any aspirin or anything
really? I've just,
I've got a little headache.
- Wish I could help.
I took the last one.
- I normally have something on me
and my stash is in the bottom
of my moving truck right now.
- You have a stash?
- Uh, no. I worked at a pharmacy
and we got a special discount. Hmm.
- Huh, sounds like a good job.
- Are those shot around here?
I love that!
- Yea, it’s just a dumb hobby of mine.
- You took these? They're
beautiful.
- Yea, there’s just something about the wide open sky
and the sunrise that calms me.
It's like a new day, a new
a new life every day, you know?
- Yeah. They kind of remind me of home.
So is there like a CVS
or anything around here?
- Nope.
But we got one of them
fancy Rite Aids.
- Okay!
Down the 58, exit Silver Queen Road.
It's about 20 minutes away.
- Thank you.
I'll see you later.
- The daily struggle for survival is a total drama.
(phone ringing)
- Super Six front desk, how can I help you?
- The creation of new life.
- I don't know what happened.
I was watching the Ted Powers sermon
and it just cut out.
- Yeah, that's not good.
We all need God right now.
- You said it right, brother.
We're right in the middle of it.
- Of what?
- The Apocalypse, man. It’ll gobble you up.
- Hey, gotchu!!
Got your ass. You're a hard man to keep up with,
I'll tell you that.
Hey, um, this towel.
It’s getting crusty in here.
Someone need you to switch that out for me
if you'd be so kind. Okay?
- Okay. Just throw it in the hallway
when you're done.
- And the wifi.
- Six feet, please.
- Yeah.
The wifi sucks. Okay!
So that's going to have to be fixed.
Alright?
- I know. I know.
- Kaboom!! Good night!
- Good night!
Just keep clean, be cool,
and stay the course.
Most of them are only here for a few days.
(knocking)
(buzzing)
- Hey, sorry to bother you again, but
I have something for you.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- How much do I owe you?
- No, please.
I got the special discount.
- Special discount?
- Mm hmm.
- I should send you on runs.
- Maybe you should.
- How's your headache now?
- Good. Better.
Does your work cover that?
- Some, but it's complicated
and definitely not all of it.
- Well, a motel chain
like this should cover that.
I mean, there are
probably hundreds of these.
They make millions.
- It's not that bad.
I mean, boss man takes care of me.
He gave me a a job, health
insurance, place to stay.
And just now, he even gave me
time-and-a-half.
I really need this job, so.
Don’t want to ruin a good thing.
My, my dad needs help paying for home care.
He got the virus
a few weeks ago. Some jerk
got too close to him at the grocery store.
- I'm really sorry to hear that.
And don't forget
to take care of yourself. Okay?
I should get back to my room.
Chad's probably wondering where I'm at.
But. um, if you ever
need to talk, I'm here.
Okay?
- You got it, doc.
- Yea. Bye.
-Bye.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you...
(beep)
Tarik, what are you up to?
- Uh, folding towels. See.
- We have a serious problem.
- What the fuck? Where's all the supplies?
- We stocked this place for six months.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
- Goddamn, Rodriguez!
She must be slipping
shit out on her purse.
- This can’t be. Fuck! Fuck ! Fuck !! Fuck !!!
No, come on, come on.
Where the fuck is it?
(bubbling)
(heavy breathing)
(hyperventilating)
What the fuck?
(maniacally laughing)
- What the fuck!!
Why? Why would you do that?
- What? I'm just trying to have
a little fun with you, Tarik.
Lighten up!!
- This isn't funny.
- You're always so fucking serious.
Man up, bro!
(laughing)
(beeping)
(door slamming)
(chuckling)
(kicking)
- Man up, bro. Man up, bro!
(muffled screaming)
Fuck you! Fuck!!
Fuck you! Fucking!! Fucking!!!
- What’s you doing? Get a hold of yourself!
He's just like all the rest.
He doesn't give a shit about you.
(phone beeping, ringing)
(beeping)
- Hi, Tarik. Melanie, again,
from Dr. Avery's office.
I hope you’re okay. It’s been a while. So please
give me a call. Thank you.
(beeping)
(cheerful music)
- This type of car was used to travel through time
in “Back to the Future.”
- DeLorean.
- DeLorean. That is correct.
This flag seen here stands for what
Democratic Republic?
- Nepal!
- Maldives?
(door slamming)
- Uh, that is incorrect.
- The right answer is Nepal.
(buzzing)
- Hey, did Chad come here?
I can't find him.
- Did you try his phone?
- Yeah. I couldn't reach him.
It's not like him to be gone this long,
and especially because he usually doesn't
go anywhere without his gun.
- Maybe he's recording another song for you.
- Could you please just help me find him?
Maybe he's somewhere around the motel.
- I can't. Gus doesn't like me
to leave my post.
I'm literally the only employee
holding down the fort.
- Okay!
- I'm sorry!
(mouse clicking)
- In the middle of nowhere in California,
and he's been missing
for a couple hours. He’s not answering
my calls or my texts.
So just trying to...
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
(beeps)
- What is she doing?
- She's looking for a boyfriend.
She can't find him.
- I don't want her looking around like that.
- Get her back into her room.
(beeps)
- Yeah, I don't want to, like, freak
anybody out, but it's been like
a few hours, and I'm just in the middle
of nowhere in California at this motel
and he's not...
- Hey.
- Hey, can I call you back?
- Thanks.
- Is that him?
- No, no, I'm just calling
literally everybody
I know to see if they've heard from him.
- Oh.
- He's not answering my calls or my texts.
- Sorry.
- Yea!
- Um, I hate to do this, but I
I can't have you back here.
Getting in trouble with my boss.
He wants me to ask you
to go back to your room.
- Okay. Well, I'm not going to stop
looking for him.
- Well, I can't. I can't have you, like,
wandering around the motel.
Umm, so if you can maybe
just go back to your room and
wait for him.
- Yeah. No, no, I get that.
I get you're doing your job,
but I'm not going to go back to my room
until I find Chad. Alright!
So I would appreciate it if
you would just help me.
- Hey, wait up!
(door opening)
- Well, there’s no use in
go and look in my room again.
I've gone back to
check a dozen times already.
(door closing)
- What was the last thing he said to you?
We got in a fight.
- I'm sure he's fine.
He'll come back.
- Thank you for helping me.
- You're welcome.
- I’ll see you around.
- The pandemic is straining relationships,
in some cases beyond repair.
Divorce rates spiking, friendships fraying, and families
want attention as they navigate
uncharted territory.
- Don't let yourself get suckered
in by this girl.
She doesn't want you.
She wants to be with her boyfriend.
Plus, you have Carolina.
You okay?
- Yeah. He's just such a child.
I told him that one of his songs
could be better and he flipped out.
He just can't take critique.
And now I'm here alone.
(giggling)
It's a little it's a little cold.
But it's nice, though.
- It is nice.
- The percentage of tests that’ve
come back positive
has tested the threshold
of 8%. It’s the equivalent of a new diagnosis every second.
- Hey!!
- Chad!! Is that you?
- Yo!! Tarik!!!
- Gus??
It's probably just Gus
messing with you again.
Don't fall for it.
Gus??
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you
(beeps)
- Get away from that
electrical closet, it’s dangerous!
- Oh, no, I heard a strange sound
coming from in there.
- No, just get away from there!
- I was just trying to open it
to check what it was.
- It's got all the hardware
and the hard drives for the cameras.
You don't need to be going in there,
so get away from there and go back to your desk!!
- Sorry!!
(beeps)
- Hey, buddy, can I get a spot?
Uh! Whoo!
- Is the AC broken?
It's like a sauna in here.
- No, no, no. Leave it. Leave it.
It's good for muscle dilation.
- You always work out this late?
- Yeah. I mean, you know, pandemic messed
up my internal clock.
I got used to working
out whenever I felt like it.
Gotta sweat it out whenever
you get a chance, you know?
Buddy. That right there!
- Huh?
- What would you pay for that?
- Oh, uh.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm not really into weights.
- 40 bucks!
All of them. It's a steal.
And if you don't have the money right now,
we can get them to do the motel checkout.
Did you know that
adding 10 pounds of muscle increases
your life expectancy by ten years?
- Who said that?
- I said that.
Go ahead lift it!
Alright, I'll give you a free
delivery to your office.
Come on.
- No, no, no, no, no, that's...
that’s... that’s...
You’re gonna be pulling chicks left and right after this.
Alright? Just give it three weeks.
- No, I just.
Hey, no worries, man. This is your loss.
But. But before you go.
I wanna give you this.
It's a gift. It's
to help deal with daily stress.
Absolutely free of charge.
Don't be nervous.
It's just Carolina.
You guys had a miscommunication.
Everything is better now.
She's had time to relax.
Pandemic just fucked us all up
like everything else.
(FaceTime ringing)
Come on, come on, come on.
- Oh, shit.
- Hey!
- Hey, Tarik!
Um, can I actually call
you back tomorrow?
Um, I have to work pretty early.
- Yeah. Yeah, no problem.
Um, what time is good for you?
- How about in the afternoon?
Like 2 or something?
- The hell was that?
- What?
- I just saw a guy behind you.
- I think you're seeing things.
- See? See? There he is again. Right, Rick.
-Alright, ‘ Rick,
we've been broken up a year. Remember?
- I dropped everything
to move out to California for you.
- How long are you gonna keep calling?
(glass smashing)
Aah. Fuck! Fuck!!
- You should have called her sooner, Tarik!
She’s slipping away from you.
Now she's laying
with some guy in her bed
and you're stuck here in this hell.
- No. Nobody’s here. Nobody’s here.
‘Rick we’ve been broken up a year. Remember?
A year ago. Remember?
How long are you gonna keep calling?
(knocking, rattling)
(buzzing)
(knocking)
- What?
- Woah.
- Sorry! What's up?
- I have a favor to ask you.
Could I, by any chance,
go through the security camera footage
to see if I could find Chad in there?
- Negative!
And that's not me.
That's strict orders from the top.
He said, never, ever!
Even if my life depended on it.
- Look, I would not be asking you this
if it wasn't important. Chad's missing!
He's not responding
to my calls or my texts,
and he's been gone for a really long time
and I'm starting to get scared.
Please!!
- Don't get stuck
in the middle of this.
It's not your fight.
Okay. But you got to be quick. Hold on.
Click through here.
And this is all the security
camera footage.
- Okay.
What is this folder called Shush?.
- Hey, can you not look
through anything else?
Can you just look
at the footage and get out?
Woah! What the fuck is that?
- What the hell is this?
- I don't understand.
- Oh, just say that from the start,
just say that from the start
if that's how you feel about my music
and my lyrics and why you...
- Where’re you going?
- If you walk out that door, Chad...
I'm gonna be so.. Do not leave me here.
Chad, don’t, don’t go...
Who's that? Chad!
(mouse clicking)
Uh!!!
Oh, my God.
(mouse clicking)
Are you fucking serious?
(humming)
I thought you were a good guy.
- No, wait, wait! It was logged in
as Gus, not me. See?
- You're a fucking perv.
- Fuck. Gus!!! What did you do?
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a
(beep)
- Tarik, what the fuck did you just do?
- What are those cameras?
- I told you never ever under any circumstances
allow anyone to see the goddamn monitors.
Over your fucking dead body.
- What are those cameras in the rooms?
- I have to keep an eye
on the guests in the motel
for our own safety. It’s a matter of life and death.
Where you think she's
going to go now, Terik?
She knows all about my cameras.
- No. She won't call the cops.
She likes me.
- Tarik, it's horseshit. It's not real.
Pull it together!!
Shit!!! Come on.
(grunting)
Hey, please. I didn't know about the other cameras.
- Don't talk to me.
- You gotta believe me please!
- Get out of my way
or I'm gonna call the cops.
(slamming)
- I swear I didn't know.
- Oh, really?
I find that hard to believe
when literally all you do all day is
look at those monitors.
- No, no, no,
it was logged on as Gus.
- Oh, okay!
How was it logged on to Gus then?
- I don't know. He's
hiding out somewhere in the motel.
Must have remote access
to all the cameras. Katy, please.
Please don't tell the police.
We'll get in trouble.
They'll shut down the motel.
I'll lose my job.
- Uhuh. Yea.
(phone keypad pressing)
(phone dialing)
- My dad can't afford his medical bills.
Without this job,
he's gonna die.
(phone dialing)
- 911. What’s your emergency?
- I'd like to report a missing person.
- Do you now their full name?
-Yes! Chad Baker!!
- Can you give a description?
- Six foot brown hair.
- Was he seen today?
- Yes. Yes.
- How long ago?
- 24 hours.
- Okay, and what is your name, miss?
- My name is Katy.
- We’ll send a unit out shortly.
- Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
(phone hangs up)
(beep)
- I’ll help you find Chad.
And I'll get rid of all the cameras.
- Is he listening to us now?
- No.
- Tarik
I think Gus is taking advantage of you.
I think he's made you his prisoner.
And you've gotta stand up to him
or he's just going to keep on doing this.
I’m gonna fix this.
(mouse clicking)
Come on. Where are you?
(key pressing)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you
(beep)
- What the hell is going on?
Why are you messing with
the cameras?
- Where are you?
- I'm right here, Tarik.
I'm right here. Look!
- Yeah?
Where in the motel are you?
- Oh, why does that matter?
‘Cause I'm down here busting
my ass while you sit back, relax
and tell me what to do.
Now. Where are you?
- First of all, it's
none of your goddamn concern where I am.
Your job is to clean
and to babysit the front desk, Tarik.
My job is to make sure that this place
does not go under.
- Yeah? What if I got sick?
- I don't know, Tarik.
Maybe I would find somebody else.
I could snap my fingers and get anybody
to do what you fucking do.
You know what Tarik? The better question is:
What if I got sick?
Then what would you do then?
Huh? Would you run this place?
- Sure as shit I could.
I already do.
- You ungrateful piece of shit!!
When I found you,
you were on the side of the road
with a”Will work for food” sign.
Who gave you a job?
I did. Who gave you a place
to stay, Tarik? I did!!
You know, you were so upset
about your ex-girlfriend, Carolina,
begging, strung out on meth,
and you don't remember any of that?
- I bust my ass for you. Don’t I?
And yet you pay me in pennies.
- You know what, Tarik?
Why don't you go out there
and see if you can find anything right
now, especially during a goddamn pandemic?
- Any place be better than this
shithole!!
Well, then, you know what? Fuck you!!!
Don't you ever come back here
begging me for your job!!
You ungrateful piece of shit!!!
- I won't.
(knocking, door opening)
- Okay, hey, let’s go out o f here.
- Woah, hey!
- Come, live with me and my dad!
- What?
- You know he isn't right for you.
He treats you like shit. I've seen it.
- Hey, no, no, no!
You don't know anything
about my relationship with Chad
Where is this coming from?
- Look! It's either me or Chad!!
- What? This is insane!
We barely know each other. We just met.
- You, you said I have to get out
of here. It was your idea.
- Oh.
- Well, where are you going?
- I gotta pee.
- Uh!!
Jesus, Gus!
Positive test results!?!
Virus confirmed!?!
Katy Jackson!?!
Get out of there!
The virus could be anywhere.
She has it. She has the disease!
- Oh. Are you okay?
(panting)
- Hey, no no no! Stop stop Tarik!
I can explain this!!
- Stay away! Stay the fuck away!!
(hyperventillating)
You can't save her!
No one can save her!!
(hyperventillating)
She did this to herself!
Forget about her, Tarik!
Just go!!
(hyperventillating)
(dry heaving)
(panting)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you.
(beep)
- Tarik. You okay?
- Yeah.
- Good. Listen!!
I'm sorry for yelling.
And, I can't run this place without you.
I don't trust anybody else.
You know your dad,
he needs you and you need me.
So there's a big circle of life.
What?!?
- She's got the disease!
- Tarik, you were around her.
I told you to be careful.
- No, I've been wearing my gear at all
times, like you said!!
- Are you sure?
We cannot have anybody here
who is infected.
(stifled coughing)
- Goddamn it, Tarik!
I'm going to kill you!!
- Fuck!!
- Tarik!!
Tarik!!! I can hear you breathing.
Open the door, Tarik!!
Open the door, Tarik!! I know you’re in there.
Goddammit Tarik!!! Open the door.
Open the door, Tarik!!
Tarik, I know you're in there!!!
Open the door right now!!!
Tarik!!! Open the door, Tarik!!
- You in there?
Come on, man. I know you're in there.
(banging)
(buzzing)
- Everything okay?
- Yeah!
How can I help you, Officer Dalton?
- I'm here to inspect the area.
We get a report of a missing person.
- Oh?
- You want to show me
some keys or something like that
so I can check out these rooms?
I’m sorry! I can't just let you go through our rooms
without a warrant.
I need to protect
the privacy of our guests.
- Okay. That's cool!
- You don’t mind if I take a look around, do you?
- Uh, yes, I mind. I don't think that's a good idea...
- You know, I didn't think you would mind.
- My boss is not gonna...
- Hey, I appreciate that. Thank you.
- Please don't!
Shit!
(radio chatter)
(squeaking noises, rattling)
(door kicking)
Holy shit!!
(radio chatter)
I'm gonna need you to get out, sir!
(coughing)
Get up, get up! Put your hands up!!
(mumbling)
- Hey!!!
- They’re all dead. Everybody’s dead!
- Okay. Hey, hey, hey! No!
(mumbling)
- No, no, you don’t undertstand.
Exploiting class.
- Easy!
- They’re shooting everybody.
(laughing maniacally)
No..no..no.
Capitalism..
is the evil. It’s evil!!
Oh God!
Damn, we've actually been looking for a guy
matching his description.
Squatting businesses all over town.
Absolute lunatic.
Anyway, about your boyfriend.
I've notified the local authorities
so they'll be looking out for him, alright?
Thank you.
- Roger that!
- Alright now!
Hey yo, Fife! You got some Lysol?
- Yea.
- Tarik!
Can we talk?
- There's nothing to talk about.
And if you're going to say something
about the cameras in the rooms,
Gus is doing the right thing.
He's just trying to protect the motel
and the business.
You'd do the same thing
if you were in his place.
- I actually wanted to talk about...
- There's nothing left to talk about.
I think you're sensible enough
to leave by dawn.
See you in the next lifetime!
(water pattering)
(dry heaving)
(scrubbing)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you.
♪ There's a call..
(beep)
- Hey, Sam!
I was just thinking of you guys.
Can I talk to my dad?
- Tarik, uh...
- Everything okay?
- Tarik, it's your dad.
He passed away earlier today.
I've been trying to get a hold of you
all day.
- No! No!!
- He was taking his medicine.
And then today he collapsed
in his living room.
He didn't even make it
to the hospital.
(sobbing)
No!!
Tarik, I'm so sorry.
(sobbing)
No!!
(dad voices)
(harmonica music)
(growling)
(whispers)
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
(beep)
(whispers)
- Hello?
- Hello Tarik! Enter!!
- Uh? Did you say there was a spill?
- You’ve come far, but you’re finished
in what you do.
Break the chain and you’ll free, too!!
(clapping)
- Hey! You okay?
Sorry, I was meditating and
and just wasn't paying attention
and just all my essential oils spilled
everywhere. I'm sorry.
What, what just happened a minute ago?
I don’t know. You came in to clean up the spill.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone for you.
♪ There's a call, there’s a call,
there’s a call for you, there’s a call
♪ on the phone..
- You motherfucker!! What is she still doing here?
- Just relax!
She's leaving in the morning!
- No,  she's gotta go!
You want the hotel to get infected?
You biological terrorist!
- It's too late to leave!
Besides, she's not going
anywhere else tonight.
- Tarik, how do you know that?
- Why are you always on my ass?
Can't you just fucking chill?
You’re fucking always on my fucking ass!!
Always with the what and why and the how!
Just fuck off!!
(glass smashing)
Just give me a fucking break, will you?
Hello?
- You motherfucker!
You're protecting her, you
little piece of shit!
No! No! I told you, it's too late to go.
- Oh, you think that I'm a moron?
I saw you two together.
You get the virus
by breathing on each other
through microscopic droplets in the air.
You can't ignore the science, ‘Rick!
And you are hanging out closer
than conjoined twins.
- No, we weren’t!
- Tarik! What makes you think that
I didn't hear you?
- Fuck!
But I didn't do anything.
(scoffs) You calling me a liar?
- I didn't get within six feet of her.
- You know what? Fine!
Maybe I'll just have to handle
the both of you like I did Chad.
- What did you do to Chad?
Where is he?
- He died from the virus, Tarik!
- You fucking killed him!
You fucking evil!
- Hey! He was coughing and sneezing.
I told him that he had to go
and he wouldn't listen.
And now your girl, she's doing the same.
- Please. Please tell her I told you
she's leaving tomorrow. Come on!
- You know what, Tarik?
If I were you, I wouldn't
be so worried about her
since you got the virus, too.
Protect your own ass!
- Please!
(laughing maniacally)
Tarik!
You can't run from your shadow!
It's coming for you!
- Tarik!?!
(panting)
Tarik! Come back, Tarik!!
(thumping of the door)
- Katy!!
Katy!!
- Tarik, over here!
- Oh shit!
- Tarik, come back, Tarik!!
- Katy! Katy!! We gotta go out of here.
We gotta go!
- Why?
- We just, just trust me!
We gotta go!
- Well, I can't just leave.
What about Chad?
- I'm sorry. He's not coming back!
- What do you mean?
- He found out!
- Who found out what? What’re you..
- Gus!!
He found out that Chad had the virus
and he killed him!
- No, no, he didn't have the virus!
- Katy, we don't have time. We have to go!
- Stop! Stop! Stop!! Chad didn't have the virus.
- Yes, he did! I saw him coughing and hacking!
- It was his allergies. That’s it!
- Katy, he's dead! He's dead!!
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
- No. No. No. No.
- We have to go! He's coming for us now!
- I have his gun. I have Chad’s gun!
- No! No! No! We should drive off.
Believe me, it won't end well.
- Tarik! Tarik!!
- Did you hear that?
- Come back, Tarik!!
- Shh shh!
- Come back!
- Why is he after us?
- Because we have the virus, too.
- That’s what I was trying to tell you - The pandemic
has been improving for months now!
- What?
- They found a vaccine!!
I don’t have the virus!
- No!
- Oh Tarik!!
- Shit!! Gus!! He doesn't know!
He won't spare anybody.
We gotta get out of here. Now!!
- Tarik!! Tarik!!
- Come on! Come on!!
You okay?
- Where’re we going?
- Oh Tarik!!!
- Oh fuck! Where is he?
- Hey, the moving truck is out front! Let’s go!
Come on!
- Shit!
The keys are in my room. Come on!
- Tarik! Come back Tarik!!
- Oh shit!
- Come back!!
- Tarik! Let’s go! Come on!!
- Tarik,ome back!!
- Let’s go! Let’s go!!
I know where to hide.
Give me the gun!!
- Do you know how to use it?
(metal rattling)
- Come on, Tarik!!
Come to daddy, Tarik!! Come on!!!
Come on, Tarik!!
(gunshots)
(screaming)
(grunting)
- Oh, shit! Oh sit!!
- Oh shit!!
- Oh my God!!
- What the fuck is she doing here?
(grunting)
- He! He!! Run!!
- Tarik!! Come back!!
- Wait, wait, wait. What is she trying to say?
(sobbing)
- Follow me, Tarik! Follow me, Tarik!!
- Follow me!
- Katy!!
- Tarik!! I’m here.
I’m here!
(heavy breathing)
- Tarik! Come on!!
- Katy!!
Come on, Tarik!!
- Tarik!
Oh Tarik!!
Tarik! You can’t run away from me!!
- Tarik, help me, please!
Tarik, help!
- Katy! Katy!
- Tarik!!
- Katy!!
- Tarik!!!
- Tarik, help me. Please!
(laughing maniacally)
(screaming)
- What’s wrong?
- Tarik!! Come on!!
(sobbing)
Come on Tarik!!
(laughing maniacally)
- Come on!!
- What the fuck is going on?
- Oh, shit! Fuck!!
(screaming)
- Holy shit!! Katy, we gotta go!!
We gotta go!! We gotta get out of here!
- Tarik!
I’m here!!
- Katy!!!
No!!!
(sobbing)
(sobbing) Tarik!!
No!!!
- Tarik!!
(sobbing)
- Oh Tarik!!
- Where the hell are you motherfucker?
Come on and show your face!
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you?
- I'm right here!
- Where?
- Look closer!
- What?
- Take a closer look!!
- What the fuck is going on?
- You don't recognize me?
- You're not me!
- No. Of course I am!
- What did you do to everybody?
- Mhm, you don't remember?
- I stood upon the sand of the sea,
and I saw a beast rise up
out of the sea, having 7 heads and 10 horns,
and upon his horns 10 crowns, and upon his heads
the name of blasphemy.
The Apocalypse is here! This is the end!!
The Apocalpyse...
(muffled screaming)
(grunting)
(heavy thwack)
(laughing maniacally)
(knocking)
(door opening)
- Heh. What’re you doing here?
What!
(smashing)
- Aaah!!
(thrashing)
- Aaaah!!!
- Dammit, Tarik. How many times do
I have to remind you to clean the goddamn rooms?
It should only be once!
- I cleaned the rooms!!
- Well, get your head out of your ass
so you can actually hear me!!
You got your ass...
(sparks and buzzing)
(thud)
- I didn't. I didn’t!
- Oh, you did! You did!!
You even killed Katy!!
(laughing maniacally)
- What's going on?
Why do you have that knife?
- You're sick!!
- No, I'm not.
I told you I'm not.
- You need help!
- Did you hurt the other people
in the motel, too?
- I helped them.
- Did you kill Chad?
(sobbing)
- You're too good for him!!
- Was it a voice in your head?
Did a voice in your head tell you to do it, Tarik?
You don't have to do this, okay?
You don't have to listen to the voice!
(sobbing)
- Okay, I don’t.
- Do it!!
Do it!!
Test results don't lie!!
She's got the virus!!
- You need help!
You just need help.
I can help you!
It's alright. It's okay. It's okay.
Just put down the knife!
- Please help me!
- It’s gonna be ok. It’s ok!
It's ok. It's ok. It's ok.
(sobbing)
(knife stabbing)
(grunting)
(sobbing)
No!!
I’m so sorry, Katy!!
I am so sorry!!
(knife stabbing)
(sobbing)
- No!!
No! But I loved her.
(laughing maniacally)
- That's funny!
- Why the fuck is that funny?
- Oh, ‘Rick, ’Rick, ‘Rick!
She was the only one
who could have come between us.
And you killed her!
That's funny. She could have saved you,
but you killed her!
But they deserved it.
They never listened to you.
Never put their masks on.
Selfish fucks!!
And Gus!!
That fuck!! He never gave a shit about
anybody but himself!
(coughing)
So dirty!! That greedy bastard
probably had the virus himself.
You did a favor!! But.
- Aah.
- Well,
I’d say I kinda liked him, you know.
You know. ‘Cause he was always
pushing you towards me!
Me and you!!
We're all we got.
(laughing maniacally)
Listen!
They all needed to learn a lesson.
- They did?
- They did!
- They did!!
- And you did good!! You hear me?
You did real, real good!!
I'm proud of you!
Now, go clean up!
But remember - Six feet!!
(laughing maniacally)
(zipping)
(gloves snapping)
(scrubbing)
- New hope on the vaccine front!
So far, more than 45 million Americans,
13.6% of the population have received
at least one dose of the two-shot vaccine.
Now released encouraging data
just ahead of the FDA meeting on Friday,
the single dose vaccine.
(camera flashing and whirring)
- Layoffs, the financial pressure
and the caregiving,
they’re all taking a toll on people
across the country.
Numbers are hard to come by,
but a recent survey
found that 65% of people say that worry
or stress tied to these outbreaks
have led to at least one negative effect
on their well-being, including things
like trouble sleeping, eating and alcohol use
People right now
who are already in support groups
or seeking treatment for things
like substance abuse or mental illness
are having an even more
difficult time than most.
Rarely these days do
we get to report on good news about the virus.
But we have these new studies.
- There's another major research,
not peer reviewed yet,
but promising which seems to suggest that people
hospitalized develop antibodies
within one week.
This means that even before
a full recovery, the risk of infection
to hospital personnel
and frontline workers is reduced.
- The other studies have found
that it takes a little longer.
But almost every study is finding
that after you've been infected
and clear the infection,
you develop antibodies.
And right now, all the evidence
point to the idea that...
(mouse clicking)
You can't see germs, but they can see you.
Mingling and scurrying
about without consequence
while they silently destroy our world.
The only way to stop them from
spreading is to kill every last one of them!!